A World Dai Star?
I know you'll be one someday, Kokona.
No way.
Even at the audition the other day...
Regarding Your Audition
Hello, Kokona Otori-sama.
Thank you very much for auditioning with us.
After careful deliberation, we regret to inform you that
you have not passed our audition.
they told me I lacked Sense.
Well, I disagree.
You don't believe them either,
do you, Kokona?
Well...
Do you know what kind of people
become World Dai Stars?
Huh? Um...
People who are really good at acting...
and singing and dancing...
People so dazzling that you just
can't take your eyes off of them?
That's not it at all!
They're people who believe
in their future selves.
You can hear them, can't you?
The voices calling your name.
I wonder if I'll ever make it...
Can I really become a World Dai Star?
You will, Kokona.
I'll make it happen.
In the twentieth century,
the passionate performances of actors
who appeared like shooting stars
ushered the world into
the great age of theater.
Kaminarimon
It became the ultimate entertainment
for the masses around the globe,
and many an actor competed
for the spotlight.
Performers with the Sense to outshine others
became known as "Dai Stars."
And the pinnacle of Dai Stars
was given the title...
World Dai Star.
Stella of the Theater:
The Girl with Dreams
At Twilight When
the Cold Wind Blows
The Little Mermaid
Become a World Dai Star!
Kokona Otori-sama
Notification of Second Audition
Shinkansen Ticket
Hachinohe
Ueno
What are you so nervous about?
I mean, who wouldn't be?
I've always wanted to join SIRIUS,
and I've already gotten
two tryout rejections.
There you go getting down on yourself.
You've rehearsed loads for this,
so you need to go in full of confidence!
Hup...
Yeah, you're right.
I finally got to a callback,
so I've gotta do my best.
There we go.
Kokona.
Oh, sorry. Did I wake you?
Here's your lunch.
You can't project properly
on an empty stomach.
Leave no room for regrets.
Right!
Off I go!
Like a rich jewel in an Ethiope's ear;
Beauty too rich for use, for earth too dear!
Did my heart love till now?
Forswear it, sight!
For I ne'er saw true beauty till this night.
Forsooth... this is true love!
You're overacting.
Huh? You think so?
You sound more like a fool than a lover.
Romeo's actually quite the playboy,
yet in this moment, he feels his destiny.
He'd probably sound way more exhilarated.
Destiny? Exhilarated?
This is...
True! Love!
Congrats. Now you're a bigger fool.
That's so mean!
I just don't get it.
I've never been in love before.
You've never been a murderer
or a detective either, have you?
But even so, an actor must
play those roles convincingly.
Then how would you do the scene, Shizuka-chan?
Huh? Me?
Did my heart love till now?
Forswear it, sight!
For I ne'er saw true beauty till this night.
Forsooth...
This is true love!
Whoa! That was amazing, Shizuka-chan!
You're supposed to be doing it.
If only you could
audition too, Shizuka-chan...
Come on. The first train will be here soon.
Oh, right!
Elisabeth
Now Playing!
Oh, Elisabeth is playing again.
I wonder if we can get tickets the day of.
There's an audition for it.
You'll pass, so it's all good.
It's me auditioning, remember?
The metro... Which one goes to... Asakusa?
Minami Urawa       Omiya
Ikebukuro   Shinjuku      Shibuya
Tokyo   Hamamatsucho  Shinagawa
Kawasaki   Yokohama       Kannai
It's basically a maze...
Konnichiwa! Um, hello?
Guten Tag? Добрый день?
Bonjour?
Oh, I know! Merci!
That means "thank you."
Guten Tag. I'm German, but you
can speak to me in Japanese.
Thanks so much!
So... where are you headed?
I'll be happy to show you the way!
Huh?
Asakusa...
Asakusa?! We're headed there, too!
Huh?
Come on! This way!
Hey—
H-Hey!
Won't You Be a Dai Star, too?
So, what did you come to see today?
Huh?
You're going to Asakusa,
so I figure you're seeing a play.
It has over a hundred theaters!
Is anything super popular right now?
Did you make it to Japan safely?
Tell me if you pass or fail your audition immediately.
Maybe... Mecha Macbeth Versus Space Hamlet?
So, what is it, Kathrina-chan?
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
Just leave her alone.
Okay...
When's the train coming?
It'll be here soon. Just keep
reading your picture book.
Little Red Riding Hood
Do you like "Little Red Riding Hood"?
Uh-huh.
Then I'll perform it for you.
Are you an actress, miss?
Uh... Not yet, but I hope to be someday.
Okay, here goes.
Once upon a time, there was a little girl
who wore a cap of red velvet.
Kaminarimon
Welcome to Asakusa!
Huh... It's much noisier
than where I'm from.
Where you're from?
Thanks for leading me here.
What? I can take you to the theater.
I'll use my navigation app from here.
Goodbye.
I see...
Nakamise
Toyotaya Shoes Shop
Koyama Shop
Oh.
I'll get as much on me as I can!
Hanayashiki Street
What?
Uh—
Well, I'm going that way too, so...
Also, the theater playing
Mecha Mac is the other way.
I know that. I'm going to the Sirius Theatre.
Sirius...
Wait, are you auditioning?!
Don't tell me...
The Sirius Theatre!
Home of the female acting troupe SIRIUS,
founded by Japan's renowned
World Dai Star, Shamo Yamabuki!
You said you saw your first play here, right?
Yeah!
The SIRIUS troupe mainly does musicals.
They're so elegant and wonderful!
I've seen them so many times!
This is where I first realized
I wanted to be an actor!
So you're auditioning, too?
Yeah!
Talk about a coincidence!
It's nice to formally meet you.
I'm Kokona Otori.
Let's do our best so we can stand on
that stage together, Kathrina-chan!
I'm not going to shake your hand.
I'm fairly certain I won't see you again.
Huh?
Frankly speaking,
you have no Sense whatsoever.
Stella of the Theater:
The heck is her problem?
She may be cute,
but she's got a rotten personality.
"I'm not going to shake your hand.
I'm fairly certain I won't see you again."
Honestly, how nasty.
That was great, Shizuka-chan!
You're so good.
You're the one she mocked.
Why are you so calm about it?
Well, I mean, it's true.
My Sense...
Noa Hiiragi
SIRIUS VP
Welcome to auditions for SIRIUS.
That's Hiiragi-san! The former Dai Star!
We are currently looking for talent
to become SIRIUS Dai Stars.
Talent we can nurture into a World Dai Star
to take the globe by storm.
I'm looking forward to seeing
your acting Sense.
We will now begin auditions,
so please gather at the venue.
You've been practicing even
more since you met me.
You can do this, Kokona.
Believe in me. And yourself.
Yeah...
I'm gonna get amazing pictures of my
future juniors at their audition!
Panda Yanagiba
SIRIUS Member
Hmm... This one's too pretty
and this one's too hot.
Reverse corrections.
Making sure their privacy is safe and...
Yup! I'm definitely the cutest.
SIRIUS Member
Chisa Sasuga
Acting's not about your face.
Shut up!
That just sounds like sarcasm coming
from a pretty girl like you, Sassu!
Also, what is that?
It's great when they loosen up.
The noodles? Or your nerves?
SIRIUS Director
Hana Kudo
This is our fifth audition, but we still
haven't found our diamond in the rough.
Kathrina Griebel,
Tobias and Theresa's daughter...
I guess we're lucky to even have her here.
I'm sure she's got it.
It's finally time to see everyone's acting.
They said you'd find out the role the day of.
We'll now proceed with the readings.
We'll also be handing out your scripts.
Thank you very much.
The Little Mermaid
SIRIUS's The Little Mermaid!
You've totally practiced this one before!
Y-Yeah...
Act 2.
The Little Mermaid swims to
the Sea Witch's lair
and asks to be made into a human.
The Sea Witch promises to do so
in exchange for her beautiful voice.
Who's the Sea Witch?
I'll be reading the part.
Hiiragi-san's doing it?
You can keep your scripts with you.
Come up onto the stage.
Let's start with number 1.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Reading with Hiiragi-san, eh?
I wonder if the boss plans to fail them all.
I'm ready.
All right.
Let's get started, then.
Once you become human,
you can never be a mermaid again.
And should the prince marry another girl,
your heart will be ripped apart.
Without even a moment to repent,
you'll disappear into sea-foam.
Do you still want to be human?
I'm asking you if you're prepared for that!
Next.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I'm prepared... S-Sea Witch...
Next.
I'm prepared! Sea Witch,
what do you require of me?
Next...
Yes, ma'am!
If they can't keep up with Hiiragi-san,
they can't express the
Little Mermaid's true strength.
But if they push too much,
they come off too strong.
This is what a Dai Star's acting looks like...
Next, number 16. Kathrina Griebel.
No set. Not even a backdrop.
Only a small spotlight
shining on center stage.
She's hiding in the shadows to capture
the Sea Witch's unpredictability.
No wonder the girls can't hold their own.
But they're all third-rate.
I'm ready whenever.
Once you become human,
you can never be a mermaid again.
And should the prince marry another girl,
your heart will be ripped apart.
Without even a moment to repent,
you'll disappear into sea-foam.
Do you still want to be human?
I do...
Are you truly certain?
Did she forget her lines?
No, she's still in character.
I'm prepared! Sea Witch,
what do you require of me?
That pause was impeccable.
She used the spotlight to her advantage,
transforming from the Little Mermaid
to a woman in love with the prince.
I think we found our promising new talent.
Thank you. You can head back.
Next up is our last candidate,
Kokona Otori.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
You've got this, Kokona. You'll be fine.
What do I do?
Maybe I can't do this... Because I...
You're going to be a Dai Star, aren't you?
Kokona? Are you listening?
don't have it...
You have no Sense.
You're not bad, but...
In this day in age, you have to have Sense.
What's the matter?
Can't play the part?
I—
You mustn't look so scary, Hiiragi-san.
Everyone will tense up.
Yae? What are you doing here?
SIRIUS Member
Yae Niizuma
I came to rehearse
for our next performance,
but I can't find Panda-san or the others,
so I'm looking for them.
It's Yae-chan!
She's so cute!
Miss, would you mind if I
did this scene with you?
Huh? Um...
What do you think you're doing?
It's only natural to help those in need.
That's what will lead to world peace.
All right.
However...
If Yae's involved, we'll
need to make some changes.
You'll be playing the Little Mermaid, Yae.
Okay.
Huh?!
Act 3.
The prince tells the Little Mermaid
he's to be engaged in a few days.
He's marrying a princess from a neighboring
kingdom who saved him from drowning.
The Little Mermaid longs to tell him
it was really her, but she has no voice.
She tries desperately to convey her
feelings, yet can't get through.
You'll be playing the prince.
This is the crucial emotional moment
leading up to the climax.
One wrong step,
and the audience's hate for the
moronic prince will ruin the scene.
Hiiragi-san's being cruel.
That's what I love about the boss, though.
What kind of performer
do you want to be, miss?
If you focus too much on being "good,"
you'll get so stiff you won't be able to speak.
What's important is what
you want to be onstage.
What I want to be?
The world you've shown me
is just so beautiful.
If only I could tell you how I really feel...
What I've wanted to be...
They're people who believe
in their future selves.
What is it? What are you trying to say?
I know! You must be happy for me, too!
I'm just the luckiest man alive!
To think that the princess
who saved me that stormy night
is going to marry me!
She wasn't like that at the station.
No... I'm the one who saved you!
What?
I'm the one who saved you!
What are you trying to tell me?
Did something painful happen?
Are you sad?
It's okay.
I'm here with you.
I'll always be on your side.
I told you so.
I knew you could do it, Kokona.
Thanks so much for earlier!
Were you waiting around
just to tell me that?
Yeah! If it weren't for you,
I would've been sent packing.
Oh, um...
I'm Yae. Yae Niizuma.
Yae-chan...
Even if I don't pass this round,
I'm going to audition for SIRIUS again!
And then, one day we can...
Hey, Kokona! Why are you talking
like you're going to fail?!
Hey! This part's really
important, so butt out!
You're a strange one.
Kokona Otori played the prince
from The Little Mermaid.
But...
Just thinking about what I'd have
done if Yae-chan hadn't shown up...
That wasn't her take on the prince.
Who exactly were you playing?
Second Stage
Copying Someone Else
Next time: "Copying Someone Else."