SIRIUS's
Yae Niizuma
She's so cute!
"Yae Niizuma, age eleven."
"A diva for a new generation that
appeared out of nowhere at SIRIUS."
The Little Mermaid
"She's gained experience from
a number of performances,
growing into a performer with talents
beyond those of a mere child actor."
They're calling her the
next big SIRIUS star, aren't they?
Future Dai Star Weekly
Wow, that's amazing!
Gosh, if only I could share
the stage with her again...
The results of your second audition
K-K-Kokona! You've got mail!
It's from SIRIUS!
The results of your...
Kokona Otori,
Thank you for participating
in a second screening.
After careful deliberation,
we'd like to inform you that
you have passed our audition.
This is your official notification.
Everyone who has passed will be
contacted with further instructions.
We will reach out separately
regarding your schedule.
you have passed
I...
...passed.
Become a World Dai Star!
Stella of the Theater:
Copying Someone Else
Yes. Everything arrived. Thanks, Mama.
Don't worry. Everything should go okay here.
SIRIUS SENTO
Is this really the place?
Well, it does say "Sirius."
Either way, let's go in.
Hello...
An otter?
Is it stuffed?
Be nice now, Dugong.
You must be Kokona.
SIRIUS President
Sirius Sento Attendant & Matron
Shamo Yamabuki
I'm Yamabuki, the attendant
and matron of Sirius Sento.
And this little one is Dugong.
Dugong?
It's a pleasure to meet you!
I'm Kokona Otori.
Um... This is a bathhouse, right?
Bath
Why, yes. Students may use
the baths as much as they'd like.
In return, you'll help out with the cleaning.
Wow, this is amazing.
I'll show you to your room.
Great! Thanks so much.
Say, Kokona. She said her name
was Yamabuki, didn't she?
Does that mean she's...
Huh?
Shamo Yamabuki the World Dai Star?!
You're going to make me blush,
reacting like that.
I happened to see your performance
during your audition, Kokona.
Really?
I found it quite mysterious.
I, uh, ended up panicking.
I'm honestly not sure how I passed.
I see.
Then I guess you'll have
to find yourself first.
Find myself?
This is your room.
H-Help me...
Kathrina?!
Y-You're...
Make sure you two get along from now on.
Huh?
I'd like to officially welcome you to SIRIUS.
I request my own room.
I can't sleep unless I'm alone.
It's part of a troupe's job to ensure
its talent is taken care of, no?
On the stage, you may end up playing
family members or lovers.
It's probably not a bad idea
to get to know one another.
We may also end up playing mortal enemies.
And hopefully you'll be able to find
something to inspire that, too.
Um, Kathrina?
I'm totally okay with this.
I promise I don't toss and turn much.
Oh, I don't snore either.
You do talk in your sleep, though.
I m-might talk in my sleep a bit, though!
Just be quiet.
What did you just say?!
All right, fine. I came all
this way to become a Dai Star.
I suppose I can deal with this.
A Dai Star?
So, when's our next show?
What role will I be playing?
You hope to take the stage so soon?
O-Of course I do.
What role will I be playing?
At SIRIUS,
anytime a new member joins,
we give them a single debut
performance during a production.
The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter
The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter!
The two of you will audition
for the lead role of Kaguya.
The lead role?
I get to play the lead role?!
Did you miss the "audition" part?
I'll be taking the lead role.
Whoever fails to get the role
will be playing the lady-in-waiting
who serves Princess Kaguya.
We'll hold the audition in a week,
the day before dress rehearsals.
Don't disappoint me.
My first script!
I wonder if Yae's playing
Princess Kaguya in the real deal.
Yae as Princess Kaguya...
So good...
She could ask me to do anything!
Even the impossible!
Hey, could you quit talking to yourself?
O-Oh, I'm sorry!
Um...
Won't this make it harder to chat?
And what's up with all the luggage?
It's really cramped over here.
Hey, you want to be a Dai Star too, right?
Is your goal to be a World Dai Star?!
That's, like, every actor's goal.
I'll give you some great life advice.
What?
You can't see the forest for the trees.
A wannabe actor like you talking about
being a Dai Star,
let alone a World Dai Star...
Wouldn't you consider that
rather presumptuous?
Dai Stars can fill theaters all by themselves.
You can't become one simply
because you want to.
Only the chosen few make it.
And you're not one of them.
You and I are competing for roles.
We're not friends.
Don't bother me more than necessary.
Hello!
People call me Panda,
the cutest girl at SIRIUS.
Want to have a bath time party with me?
Yikes, what the heck did I walk into?
Bath
Hey, can I call you Koko?
Huh? U-Uh, sure...
Sweet!
I like nicknames since they're not so stiff.
Also, no need to be formal with us at all.
We're younger than you anyway.
Right, Sassu?
The only things that should be stiff
are concrete and nata de coco.
Huh? Nata de coco?
Wait, is it even that stiff?
Now I want some nata de coco...
You don't need to take the
things Sassu says too seriously.
Thinking about them too hard
is just a waste of time.
Ah, got it...
Panda
Chisa Sasuga
Kokona Otori
Now, why are things so insanely
tense with you and Kathrin?
I'm not sure tense is the right word...
I think she just dislikes
me for some reason.
I'd like to be her friend,
but I guess she feels differently.
She said we're competing for roles.
I mean, she does have a point.
Panda
Chisa Sasuga
No matter how close you are,
if you're striving to become Dai Stars,
you're going to butt heads.
But that doesn't mean you
can't understand each other.
We're all actors, after all.
I see.
Okay!
First, I'll make her acknowledge
me as an actor!
To that end, I'll do my best
for the Kaguya audition!
Kokona Otori
Kathrina Griebel
Coffee
Royal Coffee Shop
Roasted In Store
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen Yae at all!
Niizumacchi said she'd
be camping for a while.
Camping?
Stella of the Theater:
What's Chisa doing?
Don't disturb her!
I'm sure she's waiting for
her role to descend upon her.
Man, the sun is bright.
She speaks the truth!
Well said, Chisa!
Sassu, rehearsal is starting.
I told you to stop basking in front of people.
I-I'm Kokona Otori! Thank you for
helping me out at the audition!
I love you! I can't wait to work with you!
You should've kept some of that to yourself!
Also, what's with the hand?!
Ah, that's not what I meant by love!
Yae, er, I mean...
Niizuma, your acting is just, uh...
You can call me Yae.
I'm sorry for not properly
introducing myself before now.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Yae...
Yae, we're going to begin rehearsals.
Okay.
The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter
All right, begin!
She will be here to serve your every
need starting today, Princess.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Misao.
Misao?
Yes.
I thought you'd be more comfortable
with a girl close to your age.
Misao!
Y-Yes?
C-Can I help you?
Let's play!
Huh?
Come here!
Yae's so cute!
Princess, wait!
This is the story of the ill-fated
Princess Kaguya, who was born of bamboo.
It's Japan's oldest sci-fi story.
In the play, Kaguya and her attendant Misao
grow up like sisters
and dread the day they
will eventually have to part.
That's SIRIUS's take on
The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter.
Next up is the audition scene.
Yeah.
Hey, have you ever seen
a bamboo blossom, Misao?
A bamboo blossom?
The books say they bloom
only once every 120 years.
Once every 120 years?
I hope we can see one together someday.
How pretty...
Her singing voice sounds so sweet,
but I feel sad for some reason.
This is a far more mature performance
than the innocent act she had at the start.
The song conveys her emotional turmoil
and sorrow over the impending goodbye.
Just listening to it makes
us feel her pain as well.
Yae really is amazing.
I wonder if I can perform like that, too...
Princess Kaguya
Manju
Man, starting off with The Bamboo Cutter?
Hiiragi's a demon.
It's interesting, though.
If it were any normal play,
it easily would've been Kathrina.
Well, Japanese culture is pretty unique.
For Kathrin, even the act of holding a tea cup
may come off as mannered and
make the performance unnatural.
She can fool us with her line reads,
but not with her mannerisms.
Having to become thoroughly
Japanese inside of a week...
Pretty tragic.
Meanwhile, Koko honestly lacks skill.
I wonder if what we saw
at her audition was a fluke.
Personally, I'm wondering why Hiiragi
overruled all objections and passed her.
It's a little mystery.
The key to victory is what lies within them...
Their Sense.
By the way, Sassu.
There isn't a whole box
for each of us, y'know?
Princess Kaguya
Manju
Really?
How was my performance?
Well, it was all right.
But if you're asking if it's enough
to beat Kathrina... I'm not sure.
Yeah... This is hard.
I wonder what Kaguya's thinking.
Oh, but the lady-in-waiting
role is pretty nice, too!
Are you joking?
You need to go for the lead role
if you want to be a Dai Star.
Right...
You were totally different
at the SIRIUS audition.
Your whole demeanor, enthusiasm...
I can't put it into words.
If you can do that again,
you might be able to pull it off.
You mean act like I did?
Tell me, Kokona.
How did you embody the prince then?
Back then...
Yae asked me what kind
of performer I wanted to be,
so I tried to imagine how
you'd play the role, Shizuka.
Me?
Huh... So you want to be like me?
In that case, why don't you try
doing the same thing again?
Huh?
We'll plan out how to play the part,
and you'll see it through.
The both of us will play the role!
The both of us?
How about it?
How would you perform
this scene, Shizuka?
I would...
Are you ready?
Yes!
Yes.
Ooh, so fresh and new!
Kokona came to watch every rehearsal,
but Kathrina didn't come to a single one.
We barely even saw her at the dorm.
I wonder how she's going to play it.
We'll start with Kathrina.
Panda, run the scene with her.
Roger!
Let's see what she's got.
When Japanese people point to themselves,
they point at their noses.
We put our hands to our hearts.
Even the most trivial differences can
make a performance seem unnatural.
I'm sure they think that,
because I haven't been in Japan long,
I'm incapable of expressing
Kaguya's inner life.
They can think whatever they want.
All right, begin.
Hey, have you ever seen
a bamboo blossom, Misao?
A bamboo blossom?
The books say they bloom
only once every 120 years.
Once every 120 years?
Huh... Not bad. She's moving like
someone who's worn a kimono before.
Just lovely.
I hope...
we can see one together someday.
How to Beautifully Wear
and Move in a Kimono
It's been one week since
I received this script.
That's 168 hours.
More time than I'd ever need.
Wow... She's even better than
she was in The Little Mermaid.
She feels no emotion
whatsoever towards her role.
Yet she can still pull it off
because she studied countless sources
and acquired the movements necessary
to play Kaguya from them.
The focus required to pull this together
in what little time she had
is Kathrina's Sense.
Your enemy cleared
her hurdle with flying colors.
What are you gonna do, Koko?
Next, Kokona.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
It's okay. You've got this, Kokona.
The both of us...
Hey.
Have you ever seen a bamboo blossom, Misao?
Huh... This is different from
what I saw in rehearsals.
A bamboo blossom?
The books say they bloom
only once every 120 years.
Once every 120 years?
She's playing a Kaguya who's trying
to be cheerful to hide her loneliness.
With this strategy Shizuka planned...
Wait...
Kokona?
Ah, this is...
Niizumacchi's performance.
Third Stage
Our First Play
Next time: "Our First Play."