Five princes are in love with you, Princess,
and they have been coming by
for a very long time.
Why not meet with one of them?
I won't make such a decision so lightly.
Aww...
It's hard to see Chisa's face from here.
But I believe their love for you is deep.
In that case, how about this?
What is it, Misao?
Do you have an idea?
I can see her! She's so cool!
Panda's as cute as ever today!
What if the princess marries
whoever brings her what she desires?
She's too precious!
I'm sure the love
of all five prices runs deep,
Panda Yanagiba's Sense is the ability
to read the minds of the audience.
making it hard to judge them on love alone.
So why not choose based
on something tangible?
She's going overboard.
She'll be getting a lecture later.
Stella of the Theater:
Our First Play
I'm with Future Dai Star,
the magazine that introduces young actors
who represent Japan's future.
Thank you for speaking with me today.
I'm Kathrina Griebel. It's a pleasure.
I hear that your parents back in Germany
are renowned World Dai Stars.
Did they happen to give you any
advice when you joined SIRIUS?
Yes. They told me to make sure
that my performances
instill the people of Japan
with hopes and dreams.
Your parents have received the
most prestigious German acting award,
the Reinhardt Award, three years in a row.
They're considered Germany's...
Shizuka, are you mad?
I'm not mad. I'm just at a loss for words.
Figures...
You lost the moment you copied Yae.
Yeah.
Actors who want to be Dai Stars
don't copy other actors' performances.
But at the same time, I'm not sure we
could have beat Kathrina with our plan.
Yeah, her performance was amazing!
What are you grinning for?
I'm not.
Listen.
You have to shine brighter than
anyone to become a Dai Star.
Okay!
Let's outshine the lead with your
performance as Misao, the lady-in-waiting!
Yeah!
Y-Yes?
Do you have a moment?
Kathrina's audition performance...
How did it look to you?
Huh?
You watched it, didn't you?
Tell me exactly how you felt.
U-Um...
I thought it was perfect.
Perfect?
Her expressions, movements, and the way she
delivered her lines all seemed calculated.
I thought she could've done
the play then and there.
I see.
But perfect performances
are surprisingly boring.
The newcomer performance is drawing near.
Starting tomorrow, you and Kathrina
will participate in rehearsals.
Y-Yes, ma'am! I'll do my best!
Find out who you really are before
this performance is over.
Who... I really am?
If an actor doesn't truly know themselves,
how could they become anyone else?
I know it's the newcomer performance,
but to think you've already got the leading role...
Well, I am your daughter. What did you expect?
Are you all right?
Not pushing yourself too hard, are you?
I'm fine, Mama. Don't worry. Bye. I love you.
Who I really am... Who am I, anyway?
SIRIUS SENTO
That's not an easy question to answer.
This is why people go
on journeys of self-discovery.
Ooh!
I really felt the awe of youth in that line!
Shizuka.
Yeah?
How would you describe
me in a single phrase?
Furaijinmon
2nd Year, Auspicious Day in April
An idiot.
That's so mean!
Obsessed with acting.
Aw, I guess I'll take that.
As for you... You're always so
calm and full of confidence.
You have so much that I don't.
Huh. You're pretty observant.
But you get mad real easy,
and your face is super
scary when you're angry!
You're the one who makes me angry!
See? You got mad!
Honestly...
Yummy! It's stuffed with red bean paste!
I love these ningyo-yaki cakes!
Hanayashiki
Asakusa Gate
East
Flower
You wear your heart on your sleeve,
so you suck at lying.
You're probably right.
Also, you get depressed really easily.
You're probably right about that, too.
But you're quick to get back on your feet.
That's one good thing about me, right?
Hmm...
Figuring out who you are is pretty hard.
It is, but actors need to be able
to see themselves objectively.
Objectively...
What kind of person do you
think Misao is, Kokona?
She's Princess Kaguya's lady-in-waiting
and works hard to support her poor family...
I think?
I'm asking about who she is on the inside.
Um, she's serious, smart,
loves Princess Kaguya...
And...
Once she puts her mind to something,
she always sees it through.
In that respect, she's just like us.
Yeah!
Preparing for a role means knowing yourself,
knowing the role, figuring out your
commonalities and differences,
and closing the gap one step at a time.
This is our stage!
"All the world's a stage,
and all the men and women merely players!"
Shakespeare!
Come on.
I suddenly took your hand (chasing you)
And we searched for our dreams filled
with sunshine through the trees (and ran)
When we had fun (and laughed)
It felt as though time had stopped
Right now is (slightly) special
I knew that somewhere deep
down (and if it's possible)
I want to (be with you) forever
I really don't want to leave your side
When the forget-me-nots bloom
The prayer I left with you
that day should bloom, too
I (touched) this warmth softly
Wishing that I wouldn't lose it
But some day (someday for sure)
Even if it doesn't reach (that far off place)
And you're going to take these memories with you
We can still (just the two of us) hide
And make this promise with a pinky swear
Thank you very much.
Kokona.
Thank you very much!
It'd be so much fun to share
the stage with you.
I'll always be by your side.
Yeah!
This is the first real rehearsal
for both of you,
so let's start with Misao's entrance.
Yes, ma'am.
Th-Thank you for having me!
I thought you'd be more comfortable
with a girl close to your age.
Misao!
Y-Yes?
Can I help you?
Can we stop for a sec?
Huh?
You totally just smiled now.
What made you think you should smile?
U-Um... Just because?
Don't act on "just because"!
Misao is supposed to be thrown by
Princess Kaguya's innocence in this scene!
You smiling changes everything!
I... I'm sorry.
If your acting sucks, you're going to drag
me down to your level. You need to—
Yeah, it's on its last leg.
We should probably change it out.
Hello?! We're in the middle
of a rehearsal here!
Stop making weird noises!
It's throwing me off!
Okay, one more time from the top!
Kokona, you're standing in the wrong place!
Yeesh. Now she's bossing people around.
All right. Like Kathrina said,
let's take it from the top.
Are you sure you don't
want to switch rooms?
Become a World Dai Star!
We can't relax with her around.
Don't say that.
We need to get along.
Say, Kathrina.
I wanted to ask you for
some advice about my role.
You need to work on your focus
before you even think about your role.
You're a failure as an actor if you
drop character and smile in a scene.
That's not what happened!
Um... How do I put this?
I couldn't help it
when I saw your performance.
What do you mean by that?
Your eyes looked so uneasy.
Like you were asking for help.
Uneasy?
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you trying to blame my acting?
No! That's not it!
Misao is Princess Kaguya's attendant,
so to see her lady uneasy...
Just do what you're told!
She really does hate me.
Who cares about her?
But Princess Kaguya and Misao
are supposed to be like sisters
who trust each other completely.
You may just have to tough
it out at this point.
The audience at SIRIUS
desires genuine performances
where the actors let their emotions collide.
Yae!
If you truly want to be a Dai Star,
why not strive to be genuine?
Genuine?
You don't need to force yourself to go
along with Kathrina's take.
You should perform in a way
that's true to you, Kokona.
Yae!
Y-Yes?
What do you think I should do?
How can I put on a genuine
performance with Kathrina?
There's only one way to break
a perfectly calculated performance...
Believe in the other actor and face
them head-on without running away.
You can also save Kathrina that way.
Save... Kathrina?
The only one who can save an actor
is the actor on stage with them.
What do you think you're doing?
You've been sneaking around,
following me this whole time.
I'm sorry.
I, um, just wanted
to know more about you.
What?
Princess Kaguya and Misao are
supposed to be as close as sisters.
So, uh...
I think we should learn
more about each other!
Hmph.
You can't even separate yourself from
your role. You're worse than third rate.
You're not fit to be an actor.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Just a bit shocked.
But I'm doing this to make our
performance a success!
I'm totally fine!
I need to face her head-on without running.
The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter
Newcomer Performance Today
Are you all right, Kokona?
Shizuka!
Wh-What?
I can't wait to be on that stage!
That's the spirit.
Believe in what you've been doing in
rehearsals and give it all you've got.
Thanks, Shizuka!
Listen, Kathrina.
You can't mess up this time.
You have to make this a
success no matter what.
Stella of the Theater:
...for you just grows again
Even if this is but a faint dream
that will one day fade
May this falling tear melt
with this momentary fragrance
Kathrin's completely
calculated performance...
So far, it really is perfect.
And now we're headed into the climax.
I have to... go back to the moon.
What?
On the night of the full moon this month,
messengers from the moon will come.
There's nothing I can do.
Even if I don't want to go back!
Her Sense disappeared?
What's... my next line?
I need to focus...
Um... Huh? What was it?
Sense that magnifies one's concentration
creates explosive acting skills.
But if the gears become misaligned,
that ability becomes very fragile.
It breaks like glass.
What should I do?
The only one who can save an actor
is the actor on stage with them.
I have to protect her!
Princess, I promised I would protect you.
It's all right. I'm right here.
I will protect you.
That was close!
But they managed to get through
by skipping over a whole page.
No, it's only just begun.
I'm sorry!
We're having electrical troubles,
so the platform won't turn!
What?!
Wait... Has that girl always
been in our troupe?
Princess, please take my hand.
I've come to take you back to the moon.
I don't care who you are!
I won't let you have the princess!
Come, Your Highness.
It's time to return to the moon.
You needn't say a word.
You need only accompany me.
Now, let us go.
Don't go!
Take me with you! Princess!
Princess...
She's trying this hard to try to make
the performance a success, while I...
I...
I can't stop here!
Wait.
Once I don that sash,
I will forget all that's happened here.
Before that, I'd like to say goodbye.
Misao!
Princess, no! I don't want you to go!
I had so much fun.
You were like a real sister to me.
Yes!
I'm so happy I met you.
Thank you.
My sister!
A month has passed.
Tonight, the full moon is
hiding behind the clouds.
Can you see me?
My sister...
The bamboo blossoms...
truly were beautiful.
Shizuka!
Kokona?
What were you doing onstage?
Hey.
Who is that?
Kokona.
Y-Yes?
I knew it. You...
really do have an interesting Sense.
Fourth Stage
Once Upon a Time
Next time: "Once Upon a Time."