I knew it. You...
really do have an interesting Sense.
Sense?
No, really!
Who the heck is that?
Huh?!
They can see you?!
They can see me?!
Stella of the Theater:
Once Upon a Time
"The final show of
The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter."
"Audience brought to tears by the
singing of lead actress Yae Niizuma..."
The Final Show of SIRIUS's The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter
Audience brought to tears by the singing of lead actress Yae Niizuma...
She was so amazing!
All the comments are about her, too!
Yae Niizuma starred in The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter at SIRIUS's theater in Asakusa.
As most readers probably know, SIRIUS is a female acting troupe put together by
our country's renowned World Dai Star, Shamo Yamabuki. Their performances regularly sell out,
and while SIRIUS is gaining national attention, the one who shines the brightest among them
is Yae Niizuma.
Niizuma's rendition of Princess Kaguya was delicate, and she put on a fantastic performance
that made the audience feel how strong her will was at times. Her solo during the climax was
truly a highlight, and the whole audience was brought to tears, overwhelmed with emotion
from Niizuma's song overflowing with her Sense. I definitely saw her potential as a future
Dai Star as she captivated the audience.
Yae was amazing in The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter!
She really was! I'm definitely catching the next show!
I cried every time I saw it...
I'm a Yae fan after seeing The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter!
Niizuma's talent stands out, even in the current acting world...
How is no one talking about you, Kokona?!
I'm going to go to every production Yae's in!
She's cute, an amazing singer, and such a talented actress... What a prodigy!
Yeah...
You poured your heart into that performance.
So why isn't anyone saying,
"Oh my gosh, she's amazing"?!
Oh! I found a comment about
you, Kathrina! Lookie!
Sure.
I'll read it later.
Voice call has ended
Great performance. I saw the stream. Good job getting
over that hiccup. You have some wonderful costars.
...Yes.
Have you thanked them?
...Not yet.
Man, she really is incredible!
Hey! Are you okay with that?!
Doesn't it frustrate you?!
H—
Er, no...
Hey, Ko—
Heya, are all three of you here?
Huh?
Move-in party?
A move-in party?
Yup!
It's tradition at this dorm to throw a
party after the newcomer performance.
How do your schedules look today?
You're not working today, Koko.
Huh? No, I'm not...
But how do you know that?
That means tonight...
We'll be throwing a move-in party
for Koko, Kathrin,
and Oshizu as well!
Yay.
Um... I'm allowed to join, too?
But of course!
Actually, you're all required to be there.
I-I...
Kathrin.
You! Will! Be! There!
F... F-Fine.
I can't wait to try your cooking.
Huh?
It's tradition for the newbies to each
make a dish for the party.
What? Even though the party's for us?
What can I say? It's tradition.
But...
Tradition.
I've never had authentic German food before!
Kathrina!
Let's do our best together!
Kathrina?
So be it.
Now that that's decided, let's go shopping!
Yeah.
Whoa there.
You're staying here, Oshizu.
Huh?
We're very interested in you.
Huh?!
Panda is, at least.
Huh?
I sure am! I've never encountered
such a unique Sense before.
I'm just so curious that...
See? I've got dark circles under my eyes.
I mean, it's honestly pretty cute
and makes me seem more panda-like.
Huh? Um, uh... sure?
How do you change clothes?
Or hop in the bath?
Hey, do you disappear if you
get too far from Koko?
Wait, what?
Well, I'm sure it'll be fine.
Anyway, looking forward to the food!
Kokona!
Shizuka!
Is she going to be okay?
No idea...
But I'm sure Shizuka would enjoy
some time away from me.
Let's go shopping!
You sure bounce back quick.
SIRIUS SENTO
I wonder what I should make.
Hmm...
Is there anything you'd
like to eat, Kathrina?
Like a favorite food?
Hey.
Who exactly is Shizuka?
She's Shizuka.
Okay, let me put it another way.
What exactly is your Sense?
Well...
A jungle?
We get all kinds of things from
fans after playing various roles.
We got bamboo shoots this time.
Sassu fans are just too clever!
Now, then... How much do you
know about Senses, Oshizu?
Honestly, not much.
So you really don't even
know much about yourself.
What a curious Sense.
Senses are special traits that
began emerging when actors
started desiring a higher
level of expression.
A little before the current acting scene
became known as the great age of theater,
the stage was overrun with actors.
In order for actors to survive,
special abilities were born
to help them take the spotlight
and shine the brightest.
Those are what we call Senses.
Just like animals adapt in order to survive,
I wonder if actors evolved, too.
Evolved?
Basically, we figure Senses are just
a super-amazing form of expression
that only manifests onstage.
But Oshizu, you're sorta... different.
There are actors who can awaken
a different personality
within them via their Sense
to fit certain roles.
It's rare, but there are even actors
who can change their appearance.
Nevertheless, they remain
a single actor on the stage.
It's inconceivable for another personality
to appear alongside you
that other people can see, too.
Not to mention,
you don't seem to disappear when
you leave the stage or Koko's side.
I wonder what Koko's Sense really is...
What exactly are you, Oshizu?
I'm...
As for Shizuka...
I met her during a time when I was
failing one audition after another.
To be! Or not to be! That is the question!
You're not bad, but you lack Sense.
You don't have any Sense.
You need Sense that can excite the audience.
Maybe I can't be a Dai Star.
No.
I can be a Dai Star!
I can! I can...
You can.
I was watching you perform.
I thought you did pretty well myself.
Really?
But you need to have more
confidence in yourself.
You need to stand proud
and let them know, "I'm right here!"
Your performance needs that kind of passion.
"I'm right here"?
Just watch.
Huh?
To be or not to be—that is the question.
Hey! Don't go doing that right here!
Whether 'tis nobler...
Huh?
...in the mind to suffer
The slings and arrows
of outrageous fortune,
Or to take arms against a sea of troubles
And, by opposing, end them?
Well?
Wow! Amazing!
So that's how I should've
performed that scene!
You can do it too, Kokona.
I'm Shizuka.
I'll make you shine brighter
than anyone as an actor...
I'll make you into a World Dai Star.
A World Dai Star...
Asakusa Hisago Street
Asakusa Hisago Shopping Street
So I think Shizuka
is a version of me that has
everything I've ever wanted.
A me who's good at acting,
super confident, and cool.
Though I'm too embarrassed
to tell Shizuka that.
Stop on by!
So a Sense that allows her to create
an ideal version of herself as an example?
Count me in! Got any recommendations?
Everything looks so good!
I wonder what everyone likes.
But then there'd be no need for
Shizuka to show up on stage.
Maybe these?
I think I came from Kokona's
desire to become a World Dai Star.
I don't know who I am exactly,
but I want to help Kokona
achieve her dream. That's all.
So why'd you show up on stage?
Because Kokona wanted the
play to be a success.
But...
I honestly shouldn't have done it.
Because I only exist to make sure
she can hold her own onstage.
So... I probably won't do it again.
Well, that's a waste.
But I think I finally figured something out.
When she was playing the prince
in The Little Mermaid,
Koko must've been channeling that
role through you, Oshizu.
Now then...
What's the meaning of this?
You really can wear the same costume
just by imagining yourself in it.
Must be nice.
On to the next outfit!
But why?
Stella of the Theater:
And now, we're going to be making
the home-style German dish
that Kathrina recommended...
Schuniterun!
It's schnitzel.
Schnitzel! Um...
Schnitzel
Lean pork
Block of bacon
Potatoes
Green beans
Cherry tomatoes
Lemon
Italian parsley
Panko
It's basically German tonkatsu, right?
Well... Sort of.
Japanese tonkatsu is really good too, though.
And deep-fried horse mackerel.
Come to think of it,
Kathrina, the way you eat...
Are you getting any veggies?
But of course.
Japanese vegetable juice is delicious.
27 Delicious Daily Veg
So...
How do we make it?
Huh?
Season the meat and then coat it with flour.
Then quickly dip it in the egg...
We're going to melt the butter first.
Otherwise, these'll burn.
So you're good at cooking?
I wouldn't say that, but both
of my parents always worked late,
so I was in charge of making dinner.
Okay, all set.
Could I ask you to handle the frying since
you've actually had these before?
Huh?
Huh?!
I'll prepare the side dishes in the meantime.
S-Sure...
I mean... I've studied
how to play a chef before.
This is a stage.
I'm a chef.
A master chef is born!
Ooh, that already sounds delicious!
Smells great, too.
Hmm? Is that smoke?
What?!
To be or not to be—that is the question.
Hamlet?!
I guess it's true that
no one is twice blessed.
Does that mean...
You actually suck
at everything besides acting?
What?! I'm sure I would've
been fine if this were a play!
Are you sure?
I think so... probably.
I see. So there are things
even you aren't good at.
Is that a problem?
No, it's fine.
I'm just happy that I got
to learn more about you!
I didn't know anything about you
except that you're an amazing actress.
I'm not a good actress either.
Even you must've been disappointed in me.
Huh?
Everyone in my last troupe was.
I always performed alone.
I forced my costars and the staff to follow
the ideal performance in my head.
The only reason they tolerated me is because
I'm the daughter of World Dai Stars.
But...
I ruined an important performance.
I was supposed to succeed.
For my costars, the audience...
For my parents...
Yet I couldn't move. And now here again, I...
Say, why don't we go ahead and try again?
Huh?
I've messed up a bunch of times, too.
I failed a bunch of auditions,
Shizuka always yells at me,
and I lost the Princess Kaguya role.
But I don't think I'll ever forget
your performance as Princess Kaguya.
Because it was our first play!
Next time we do The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter,
let's both do our best
and get even more applause!
Kokona.
I'll do this, too! Teach me how!
Sure!
And... thank you.
Sure.
Okay! Is everyone here?
Yes!
Hiiragi... What's the matter?
Don't worry about her.
She's just relieved now
that the play is over.
She had a lot of stress pent up.
She was apparently sleeping
all day in her room, too.
It's like night and day...
Uh, why are you two so close?!
Look who's talking.
Well, I'm Kokona's Sense!
Why are you two so eager to fight?
Sorry I'm late!
Taiyaki
Yae?!
What gives?!
We invited her as a surprise!
They were kind enough to include me.
Also, I brought some taiyaki.
What an angel.
Come sit over here!
What?!
Thank you.
Okay! Now we can officially
welcome you to Sirius Sento!
Cheers!
The
Star
of
Asakusa
My mouth is full of Germany.
What does that mean?
Is this a dish from your
homeland, Kathrina?
Yes... Though Kokona made most of it.
But you got a lot better at it,
Kathrina.
Koko and Kathrin seem
to be getting along great!
Well, they are roommates,
so that's probably for the best.
But how do you really feel?
I hate it! I feel like she's
taking Kokona from me!
Ooh.
Don't make me admit that!
Are you good at cooking too, Yae?
Why did the newbies cook?
Huh?
You mean it's not a dorm tradition?
First I've heard of it.
"Let's give Kathrin an opportunity
to apologize to Koko!"
"Her being so pouty is honestly a pain."
That's what Panda said.
Heh!
What?!
Oho...
I-I wasn't being pouty!
Who asked for your help anyway?!
What? I did you a favor.
I'm sure you're thinking, "Thank you,
Panda! You're super adorable!"
That's what your
heart of hearts is saying, no?
No, it's not!
Oh, come on now!
Some rather interesting girls
have joined the troupe.
Yes. I think I'm finally starting to see it.
Panda, Chisa, Yae, Kathrina,
Kokona, and Shizuka...
I'm sure something will be born
once their Senses collide.
I'll do my best to nurture them...
into World Dai Stars representing SIRIUS
and following in your footsteps.
I see.
North! Let's go north!
Will you be okay all by yourself?
I'll be fine.
Don't worry, Mama.
No, Kathrina... Don't go that way...
I'm not alone anymore.
North, north...
All right, so that will be our next play.
Yae's starring again?
Well...
Come in.
Pardon me.
What's the matter?
I have a request regarding our next show.
Fifth Stage
A Request
Next time: "A Request."