I wonder what it's doing.
Who knows?
Isn't that the spot you cleaned, Kathrina?
Huh?
Wait...
Wha— Is it telling me to redo it?!
How dare you, you little rodent!
You'd better do what Dugong says.
Dugong is famous for having a certain jinx.
A jinx?
Any actor that Dugong takes
a liking to becomes a Dai Star.
Dugong-chan!
You're so smart!
Come right on over to... Kokona's lap!
Come on!
Can you be any more obvious?
Good day, everyone!
Hello, Dugong-san. You're
still as cute as ever.
Well played, lead runner in the race
to become the next SIRIUS Dai Star.
Dugong's completely under her spell.
Oh, Yae-chan!
She's as beautiful as a painting!
It's just some rodent. Just you watch.
Shake.
You poor fool, Kathrin.
Say goodbye to your dreams
of becoming a Dai Star.
I need you all at the rehearsal hall, now.
We've decided the cast
for our next production.
Our next production?
Arabian Nights
We'll be doing...
"Arabian Nights."
Stella of the Theater:
A Wish
Our story takes place in a desert city
in the Middle Ages.
We will be focusing on one of the most
prominent stories from Arabian Nights...
"Aladdin and the Enchanted Lamp."
That's a pretty flashy piece.
She said they've decided the cast already.
Are they not doing auditions?
At SIRIUS, the sponsor and
director decide on the cast.
Hiiragi-san used to always play the
lead. Now, it's usually Yae.
Ever since Hiiragi-san retired, people say
that SIRIUS is a troupe without a Dai Star.
SIRIUS's current objective
is to make Yae a Dai Star.
Then what was the point in auditioning?
If you feel overlooked,
prove you're better than her.
That's what we're all trying to do.
Our primary goal right now is to have
people talking about SIRIUS way more
than when Hiiragi-san was in it.
Yae-chan has the Sense and
popularity to do just that.
Why did Hiiragi-san retire?
Haven't you heard, Kokona-chan?
You can only be on stage with
SIRIUS until you're 23.
What? Really?!
That's what Shamo-san decided.
She said it's not good to be
stuck in one place for too long.
What should I do, Shizuka-chan?!
I only have seven years left!
Well, bring it.
Let's make you a World Dai Star by then.
What?!
Pipe down over there.
Sorry!
Arabian Nights
Aladdin
Genie of the Lamp
Princess Leila
Sultan
Abdullah
I'll now announce the cast.
Role Name
Aladdin
Genie of the Lamp
Niizumacchi will probably play
the lead role of Aladdin.
But...
Aladdin
Genie of the Lamp
Princess Leila
The role of the Genie is
basically just as important.
If I were able to get that role, I
could bring out the best in Niizumacchi
while still showing off my own charm.
Aladdin
Genie of the Lamp
Princess Leila
What the Genie's actor needs
is control on the stage.
It appears I'll have my
second chance already.
I'll overshadow the lead.
Give Kokona a role where she'll stand out,
give Kokona a role where she'll stand out,
give Kokona a role
where she'll stand out!
I'm gonna have to learn magic.
Arabian Nights
Aladdin
Genie of the Lamp
Princess Leila
The lead role of Aladdin
will go to Kokona Otori.
Huh?
Next, the Genie of the Lamp...
Yae Niizuma.
Yes, ma'am!
Really?
A newbie is playing the lead?
Yae's playing the Genie?
That doesn't seem to fit at all.
The Royal Princess, Leila...
Chisa Sasuga.
But I wanted to use magic.
The Sultan...
Kathrina Griebel.
What? The Sultan?!
Your answer?
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Aladdin's nemesis, Abdullah...
Panda Yanagiba.
P-Please wait a second!
What?
Niizumacchi's playing the Genie?
I mean, that's one thing, but...
A newbie's playing Aladdin?
That's inconceivable!
This was decided after careful discussion.
But...
I-I'll do it.
I'll make sure this play is a success!
Please let me do the part!
I'll do my best, as well.
All right.
Princess Leila
Sultan
Abdullah
Th-The S-S-S-Sultan?
Arabian Nights
Aladdin
Kokona Otori
Genie of the Lamp
Yae Niizuma
This is your big break, Kokona!
Y-Yeah. I need to do my best...
So that Panda-chan and the
others acknowledge me.
And the audience...
And for yourself! You're one step
closer to becoming a Dai Star!
Yeah...
May I have a moment?
Uh, yes!
Schedule
5:30 Wake up
6:00 Get dressed and clean
7:00 Breakfast
8:00 Morning training
(*details on another sheet)
10:00 Break
10:20 Rehearsal/Lesson
12:00 Lunch
13:30 Afternoon training
(*details on another sheet)
15:45 Break
16:00 Rehearsal/Lesson
18:00 Bath
19:00 Dinner
20:30 Study
Stretches
From now until the production is over,
you'll be following that regimen.
You need to get the fundamentals of
stage acting down once and for all.
The fundamentals of stage acting?
You understand, don't you?
Right now, you don't have
the stamina or talent
to be up on stage for 90 minutes
in the lead role.
Then why did you pick Kokona
for the lead role?!
For SIRIUS.
No part-time jobs
until after the final show.
SIRIUS will make sure you're
taken care of in the meantime.
Glance through that regimen by tomorrow.
What does she mean that it's for SIRIUS?
| 30 minutes | 10 minute Break
| m dash | 10 minutes | Interval 1
| Squats | 15 x 3 sets | Interval 1 min
| Push-ups | 15 x 3 sets | Interval 1 min
| Lunge | 15 x 3 sets | Interval 1 min
| Crunches | 15 x 3 set | Interval 1 min
| Squat jumps | 15 x 2 sets
| Hip lifts | 60 seconds x 3 sets
| Bird Dog |
| Leg |
15 x 3 sets
15 x 3 sets | Inter
15 x 3 sets | Interval 1
15 x 2 sets | Interval 1 min
60 seconds x 3 sets | Interval 1 minute
30 seconds x 3 sets | Interval 1 min
Interval 1 min
What in the world is this schedule?
Kathrina-chan
I added you!
Okay.
Today
Hopping home
Wait right there
What's that?
This definitely doesn't seem
like it's from Kathrina-chan.
Good evening.
Um...
Oh, come on. You don't need to be so scared.
Here.
Th-These are...
Arabian Nights
Scripts from past productions of Arabian
Nights our senpais at SIRIUS performed in.
They're from my secret SIRIUS collection!
Our senpais wrote in a whole bunch of notes.
I figured they might help
you understand your role.
I can borrow these?
But of course!
Hiiragi-san chose you, and you said you
were going to see the role through.
So I've... made up my mind.
I'm sorry for being so rude earlier.
Panda-chan...
Let's make this production a success.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
I added you!
Okay.
Today
Hopping home
Wait right there
I see.
These notes suggest that everyone had
a hard time getting this role down.
Yeah.
A manly Aladdin, a timid
and unreliable Aladdin...
Even though you're surprised by Genie, make sure
you don't forget the excitement of something starting!!
Genie: Ah!
Aladdin
...merchants...
...don't look down.
They're so busy running their shops...
No one even sees me...
No one even knows my name...
The apple I stole from the merchant...
Who...
An Aladdin whose life in the grueling
desert has made him detached.
They're all completely different.
That just means the character
of Aladdin lacks any core.
Core?
The roles of the Genie,
Abdullah, and Princess Leila
are all written out in great
detail in the scripts.
Aladdin: Everyone's desperate to survive.
At night, they all get drunk to the music.
You can smell the sweet aroma and hear the laughter...
See? It's starting again tonight.
Say each of
these sentences clearly!
But there's no solid direction for Aladdin.
Which means his character takes a lot
from the actor's personality.
Aladdin: ~Sings~
I love this city!
Everyone's desperate to survive.
At night, they all get drunk to the music.
You can smell the sweet aroma and hear the laughter...
See? It's starting again tonight.
~Sings~
Make sure your body...
Don't let this line get drowned out.
It's important
At least, that's what I think.
The actor's personality...
With that in mind, it's really easy to
imagine how Niizuma would play Aladdin.
The Little Mermaid
Yae-chan's innocence.
That alone is enough to bring
her characters to life.
The audience will surely enter the world
of Arabian Nights through Yae-chan.
What makes Niizuma scary isn't
just her singing Sense.
Her ability to make each character
feel like they're actually her...
I hate to admit it, but I don't
have that kind of charm right now.
I wonder what kind of Aladdin
I should try to play.
We'll just have to try out various versions.
Ahem.
You'll need someone to
practice with, won't you?
Uh, hello? I'm right here.
Well, three's always better than two!
You're going to help me?
If you end up messing up this role,
I'll seem like a failure, too,
since you got the role instead of me.
More importantly, if you don't do this
role properly, I'm going to upstage you!
As the Sultan?
I think that itself could ruin the play...
And that's exactly why you
have to work hard, Kokona!
Good evening!
Yae-chan!
What are you doing here at this hour?
Didn't Hiiragi-san tell you?
Tell us what?
I'm going to be living with Kokona-san
until the production starts.
Huh?
Living with...?
I look forward to our time
together, Kokona-san.
Or rather... Master.
Stella of the Theater:
"Dear Kokona Otori-sama."
"I heard that you've agreed
to take care of our Yae
in order to help her prepare for her role.
I do apologize that we are greeting you
by letter rather than properly in person."
"Ever since she was little, our daughter was
very aware of her surroundings,
Would you like me to help you?
N-No! Yae-chan, you can
just make yourself at home!
filled with compassion,
determined and uncompromising once
she sets her mind on something.
Everyone often compliments her,
saying that she's an absolute gem,
but sometimes this is not the case..."
Isn't this overly long?
I mean... I can tell that your parents love you...
But what's this about
preparing for your role?
Yes. Aladdin and the Genie go through
good times and bad together after they meet.
I thought it was necessary to be in sync
with Kokona-san, who's playing Aladdin.
I did actually tell Hiiragi-san
about this earlier.
Oh.
Is something wrong?
No.
It's not a big deal.
More importantly, about this part...
I would've cleaned up if she'd told me!
So, yes. From today until
the production starts,
as the Genie that serves Kokona-san,
I would like to take care of you, Master.
M-Master?
Wait a second! You're planning
to stay in this room?!
It's cramped enough with Shizuka here!
I heard everything.
Why do you two always
show up at times like this?
The walls are paper thin.
We'll take real good care of Kathrin.
Huh?
Next, we're going to
investigate Kathrin's Sense!
Hey! No! Your room's sorta scary!
K-K-Kokona!
Maybe we should've stopped them?
Let's treat Kathrina to some
ice cream sometime soon.
But for now...
Your wish is my command, Master.
I shall grant you any wish at once.
If it is within my power, of course.
Let us savor this happiness.
Yes.
Good morning, Master!
Yae-chan? Good morning...
I'm the Genie! Now, time for
your morning rehearsal!
Let's give it our all today!
G-Good morning!
Were you able to meet your quota?
Yes, I made it. Three kilometers.
I see. In that case, hop
right into vocal training.
Tongue twisters.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
She's a demon.
Thank you for the food.
What are you doing?
An assignment from Hiiragi-san.
I have to do a scene as a different
character each morning.
Tomorrow is Macbeth.
The day after that, Tony.
After that, there's Jekyll,
Hyde, Inspector Javert...
All male roles.
I wonder why.
I-I mean... if you need someone to read
with you, I guess I wouldn't mind.
Really?! It starts with Act 3, Scene 2!
Don't sit pigeon-toed!
Separate those feet.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
When playing a male character,
you'll use big gestures.
Focus power in your fingertips.
Think about every movement you make.
Yes, ma'am!
In the morning, I have to work
out and practice the basics.
In the afternoon, I have a table read,
then singing and dance lessons.
At night, I have a one-on-one
with Hiiragi-sa—
This is going to continue
for three months?
Oh, Dugong-chan!
Did you come to cheer me... up?
I'm home.
Welcome back, Master.
Your futon has been laid out for you.
Whoa, thanks!
Um... I just can't get used to this.
Could you just call me Kokona?
Well, that's strange.
I could've sworn my master's
name was Aladdin.
That's Yae-chan for you...
She's not breaking character.
I'm kidding. If you so desire,
I'll stop for today, Kokona-san.
You did amazing work today.
What an absolute gem.
But...
Am I really going to make it,
practicing like this every day?
Is this training difficult for you?
Not exactly, but...
I know the fundamentals are important...
But you've had no time
to prepare for your role.
I've been trying to figure out a bunch of
things while Kokona's at school, but...
What kind of Aladdin
should I be playing?
I...
There's still time before the production.
You don't need to rush.
Really?
Yes! Not to mention...
The Aladdin you should play is quite obvious.
Huh?
Aladdin meets the Genie, and ends up
trusting him because of how devoted he is.
It's not because he can use magic,
but because Aladdin has spent all his
life trying to survive in a desert city,
and the Genie is the first
friend that he can trust.
Can you trust me, Kokona-san?
Yes... I can.
Then it's simple.
That's exactly how you should
pursue the role of Aladdin.
And then...
I'm sure this production will go well.
Right.
If I'm with you, Yae-chan, I'm sure...
Kokona?
Here you go, Master!
Thanks...
Yae-chan, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Why are you playing the Genie
instead of the lead role?
If I want to become a Dai Star,
I need to show everyone a new Yae Niizuma.
A new you?
Yes.
Innocent and pure maidens like the
Little Mermaid and Princess Kaguya...
I thought those were the kinds of
characters people wanted from me.
But...
I realized that I couldn't get closer
to becoming a Dai Star by only playing
the roles people wanted from me.
So you're working to become a Dai Star, too?
Of course!
Arabian
The poster came out quite nicely.
Yeah...
First, I'll become a Dai Star at SIRIUS.
Then, a World Dai Star.
And then, finally...
Finally?
Arabian Nights
No, it's nothing.
Is it really okay for me to play the lead?
What if I really mess up?
It'll be okay.
I'm the Genie of the lamp!
You just need to tell me
what you wish for, Master.
And then, I'll make it come true.
Then I have two wishes.
I wish for this production to
be a success. And...
I wish for you to
become a Dai Star, Yae-chan.
That's...
A very lovely wish.
You're not going to sleep yet?
No, it's just...
Something still doesn't sit right with me.
Why was Koko-chan chosen for the lead role?
Oh... I get it now.
She's supposed to be... the foil.
Sixth Stage
No One Is Looking at Me
Next time: "No One Is Looking at Me."