Arabian Nights
Opening Day Sold Out
Starring
Aladdin
Kokona Otori
Chisa Sasuga
Princess Leila
Yae Niizuma
Genie of the Lamp
Five minutes to curtain up.
All sections, get ready.
Koko—
Kokona!
Let's make this a great opening night!
Th-That's my line!
I c-can't wait to perform together!
No need to worry. Just think
about how much we rehearsed.
Yeah...
Master...
Trust me!
Okay.
Stella of the Theater:
No One Is Looking at Me
Ah, tonight is the full moon!
Let us enjoy this Arabian
Night to our heart's content!
I'm Aladdin.
I'm Leila.
This time, I want you
to know who I truly am.
Yes, no more lies. I want to
get to know the real you.
I order you, Genie of the Lamp!
Make me the sultan of this kingdom!
My wish is for you to be happy, Master!
But this isn't over!
I'll become the master of
the lamp once more, and...
Aladdin. This time, you're going
to grant my wish, aren't you?
I'm counting on you.
It went great, didn't it?
Yeah.
Merchandise Area
Kathrina was so cool as the sultan!
Sasuga was so pretty as Princess Leila!
Panda was so perfect as the villain!
Individual Photos 330 yen
Hey, let's go buy some merch!
Great idea! Let's go!
What?! Yae's photos are all sold out?
We're terribly sorry.
Okay!
Kokona.
Oh, Shizuka. What's up?
Kokona, can we talk for a bit?
Sorry! I promised Yae I'd
practice some songs with her.
But tell me what you thought
of the show later!
Yae Niizuma & Kokona Otori
Private rehearsal
I see you made it through the first day.
Hiiragi!
Thanks for today!
Um... How was the performance?
Uh, um...
Continue practicing the fundamentals.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
It was all so new yet so nostalgic
We were dreaming the same dream
Faint memories, predictions of the future
We lived through the same time
Every time I hope that something will change
I just keep getting more scars
So I went ahead and just cast
my eyes down coldly again
My time of imprisonment had passed
And you patted me on the head
I wanted to keep believing in this light
Coffee
So I kept trying to hold these tears back
You are the first person (Who brought this)
Become a World Dai Star!
Sun-colored future with you
(Where) did you come from?
It's like magic
We can be honest
(Our bluff unravels in the wind)
Even this season where our way
home is fragrant feels dear to me
Faint memories, predictions of the future
The sign that we're spending
this time together
Arabian Nights
Sold Out    Thank You
Starring
Aladdin
Kokona Otori
Chisa Sasuga
Princess Leila
Yae Niizuma
Genie of the Lamp
So Arabian.
They're all gifts from Sassu's fans.
Uh... Even that?
Actually, I bought this.
But why?
You know...
We've been selling out each show.
There's been nothing but
rave reviews from the audience.
The critics have nothing but praise.
And the day that Niizumacchi
becomes a Dai Star draws near.
But is this Arabian Nights
run really okay?
If you're hinting at something,
just spit it out.
Koko's performance.
It's been solely for Niizumacchi, hasn't it?
Yeah. She's just being the foil.
Is that how a star should be?!
Usually, supporting roles
make the lead shine!
Yeah.
The one who should be carrying
the story isn't doing it.
But Kokona's performance is
definitely getting better.
Exactly!
That's what's bugging me even more!
I'm getting dark circles
from losing sleep over it!
You're like a real panda. It's cute.
Well? How was today's show?
I felt nothing from your performance.
Huh?
I couldn't understand the Aladdin
you were trying to play at all.
Because you're only performing for Yae.
Th-That's not...
Can you really deny it?
The play's gotten great reviews,
and the audience seems satisfied.
But right now, your performance is bland,
like you're trying to stay out of Yae's way.
This is our first lead role.
At this rate, you'll just
end up Yae's foil.
You understand that, don't you?
So let's try this together one more time—
Sorry!
I have another show tomorrow,
so I'm gonna go rest.
Kokona...
You said you'd grant me
any wish, didn't you?
Yup.
As long as you're the master of the lamp,
I'll grant you as many wishes as you want!
Oh! But I can't bring anyone back
from the dead or control anyone's mind!
But it can be anything else?
Sure can! I'll grant you any wish.
I am the Genie of the Lamp, after all!
I'm sorry, Shizuka,
but I'm having so much fun right now.
I mean... I'm on the stage I always
dreamed of, performing with Yae!
Genie?
Hey! You don't believe me, do you?
I don't care if I'm the foil.
As long as this play is a success...
As long as the audience is happy!
Huh?
I'm not so sure about a genie
looking like you do...
Well, you can't judge a genie by its cover!
They're not looking at me?
No one is looking at me.
Stella of the Theater:
Koko?
Every human who's ever met me
gets stunned into silence,
but I guess it took you a bit
longer to get there!
The stage is going to go dark.
Let's regroup from there.
All right! Let's try this
again and have some fun!
She's so good.
She managed to turn Koko's
mistake into a laugh.
Don't make us sweat like that.
I didn't notice because I've been so swept
up in my performance since the first day.
All this cheering and applause is for...
I'm so sorry!
I can't believe I forgot my line
after we rehearsed so much.
It's perfectly fine!
I'll make sure to cover for you,
no matter what happens!
Let's put it behind us and
prepare for the next show.
Okay...
Kokona.
Can I have a word with you?
You couldn't concentrate at
all during that performance.
I'm so sorry.
There's no show tomorrow,
so make sure you get plenty of rest.
Resting is also part of your job.
Yes, ma'am.
BATH
What am I supposed to do?
Shizuka, what would you...
Huh? Shizuka?
Come in.
Pardon me.
Hiiragi, do you have a moment?
What is it?
Do you think this production of
Arabian Nights is really benefiting SIRIUS?
What do you mean by that?
I'm honestly not sure if it's good for SIRIUS
when the star of Aladdin is being
used as a foil for the Genie.
Am I the only one worried about that?
What's Shamo saying about it?
I'm the one in charge of this production.
She's leaving everything to me.
Then how do you feel about it?
How do you feel about our current
production of Arabian Nights?
How do you feel about it, Panda?
Well...
I honestly don't think it
represents SIRIUS at all.
Panda...
The reason you made Niizumacchi the
Genie is to make her a Dai Star.
I completely understand that
this benefits SIRIUS.
But if that's the only reason
you decided to use Koko,
I'm honestly disappointed.
Please excuse me.
Dear Kokona,
I have to go help out at a charity.
We don't have a show today,
so please get plenty of rest.
Yae
A letter?
I have to go help out at a charity.
We don't have a show today,
so please get plenty of rest.
Yae.
Shizuka still hasn't come back.
Shizuka?
Where are you, Shizuka?
Coming...
G-Good morning...
Morning.
Um... Has Shizuka been by?
Nope.
I actually haven't seen
Oshizu for a while now.
I see...
Th-Thanks.
Asakusa Hisago Street
Asakusa Hisago Shopping Street
Coffee
Roasted In Store
Royal Coffee Shop
Toyotaya Shoes Shop
Koyama Shop
I can't find her anywhere. Where did she go?
You should totally see
SIRIUS's Arabian Nights!
Yae Niizuma is wonderful as the Genie!
Right?
Who's playing Aladdin?
Oh, um...
It's some new girl... Who was it again?
You two are awful!
Oh, who cares? As long as
we get to see Yae!
It honestly doesn't matter who's
playing the other role anyway.
Oh, yeah! And Yae's song was totally...
Kokona?
Kathrina?
Oh, u-um...
You're not going to use it... are you?
Thanks.
Why did you want to join SIRIUS, Kokona?
Huh?
I'm pretty sure I told you before,
but I joined SIRIUS
to become a World Dai Star.
That's why I have no intention
of losing to you or Niizuma.
Keep your head up!
Huh? What?
You're the star! If you don't
know what to do as the star...
we can't support you in support roles,
no matter how hard we try!
Kathrina...
Not to mention,
when you play a lead at SIRIUS,
you're one step closer
to becoming a World Dai Star.
You can do it too, Kokona.
I'll make you shine brighter
than anyone as an actor...
I'll make you into a World Dai Star.
A World Dai Star...
I made a promise with Shizuka...
Kathrina!
Thank you!
U-Uh...
I have to go!
I need to do my best, too.
Oh, Shamo!
Shh...
I'm sorry! Um, have you seen Shizuka?
Have a seat.
Oh, but I...
It's fine.
O-Okay...
When I'm watching you, it reminds
me of how Noa used to be.
You mean Hiiragi?
Whenever it came to the plays,
she'd try to do everything herself,
unable to see what was going on around her.
She doesn't seem like that, does she?
She doesn't.
Noa's Sense allows her to see all of
an actor's skills and where they excel.
Don't worry.
She chose you two for that role because
she knew you could handle the lead.
Us... two?
Yes. She knew that you and
Shizuka could handle it.
Senses come alive on the stage.
Shizuka!
I'm sorry...
I went off and did what I wanted
to do without even hearing you out.
But I still want to do it.
With you, I want to become...
a World Dai Star!
Took you long enough, Kokona.
Let's go back over the role.
Yeah!
So that we can play...
our version of Aladdin...
to outshine all others!
Seventh Stage
Believe in Yourself
Next time: "Believe in Yourself."