Acting?
Yes. You have a Sense that would
shine brilliantly onstage.
Sense?
Why not come to SIRIUS?
If you're interested at all,
come check us out.
The Little Prince
It was like a dream.
When she speaks, everyone's enraptured,
drawn into the story.
When she looks sad,
we all feel it.
When she smiles...
She was the one who taught me that theater
is beloved throughout the world.
That it brings happiness to so many.
I wonder if I can do that too...
Stella of the Theater:
Believe in Yourself
Arabian Nights
"I need to get better for Yae's sake..."
That's all I could think
while playing Aladdin.
You need to get more familiar with the role.
Yeah.
All right!
Arabian Nights
I'm going to try playing various versions
of Aladdin, so make sure you watch.
Okay!
Established in 1962
Thank you very much.
Coffee
We'll send you the interview article soon.
Great. Thank you very much.
You have so many press requests,
I hardly know what to do.
If possible, I'd like to do them with Kokona.
Now that theater is so mainstream,
audience-goers are connoisseurs.
It doesn't matter if you're the lead.
If an actor has no presence, they vanish.
It's because Kokona is working so hard
that I'm able to play the
Genie the way I want.
Is it guilt that's making you
worry so much about Kokona?
Huh?
You had a hunch that this
would happen, didn't you?
Not giving your all up on that stage
isn't just rude to your costars.
It's rude to the audience.
You don't need to worry about that.
A kind Aladdin, a powerful
Aladdin, an anxious Aladdin...
I played various versions,
so which one felt right?
You really are amazing, Shizuka.
If only I could act like that too!
You'll be the one on stage, remember?
Anyway, I guess you'll just have
to try various Aladdins for yourself.
You mean I'll have
to change it up each time?
You'll be working to perfect the role.
I think that's the only way.
I'm not going to cause trouble
for everyone, am I?
Please!
I don't even know what to say to that...
Oh, I found her.
Weren't you going to rehearse with me?
Er...
What are you looking at?
Kokona just said something
really interesting.
Please!
We promise it'll work out!
If you change the way you play the role,
we have to change the direction, too.
And wanting to do that
for every performance is...
The lead changing the role with each show?
I've never heard of anything like that.
It would also mean changing up
our interactions with her, right?
The other actors and staff won't
take kindly to grandstanding.
Experimental acting during
a real show is unprofessional.
Shouldn't you take care of that beforehand?
The production's going pretty well so far.
Just learn from this for next time.
Isn't that enough?
It's not!
If I give up now, I don't think I'll
ever be able to take the stage again!
Please, let us do this.
Please!
Talk about selfish.
My parents are both pretty nice,
but they fight a lot when it comes to acting.
Neither one ever backs down.
They've both told me
that World Dai Stars should
be just impertinent enough
to never relent until
they get what they want.
I'm fine with it.
This'll put the most stress on you, Yae.
And there's no guarantee it'll go well.
That's all right.
I'll figure things out.
Yae...
I'm fine with it too.
Not that I have that many
scenes with Aladdin.
I have a lot, but I'm cool with it.
You are?
The Leila within me said, "Squee."
Leila doesn't say, "squee"!
Well, I'm fine with it too.
Panda!
It's totally illogical, unprofessional,
and a whole mess of trouble...
But hey, it sounds fun.
What do you say, Hiiragi?
Very well.
But you only get to change up
your performance once.
Any more would be too much
of a burden for everyone else.
If you need to get the role down,
do it tonight.
And if she doesn't?
Then she'll continue playing
the role as she has been.
Even if that means Kokona
will never take the stage again.
Huh?
Thank you very much!
We'll hold a meeting tomorrow morning.
Then we'll do a light dress rehearsal
just prior to showtime.
Inform the other staffers.
Understood.
This won't be easy,
but I'm counting on all of you.
Thank you!
Do your best.
I will!
Come with me.
Uh, okay!
We should get back to rehearsing.
Right.
What's wrong?
Did Hiiragi just... smile?
It took you too long to find the answer.
Huh?
Come in.
Shizuka.
Y-Yes, ma'am?
You said that you two were
practicing various Aladdins, right?
Did you mean the versions
others have played before you?
Yes.
Forget all of that.
Huh?!
There's no point in imitating other actors.
Let's start right now by
doing one scene at a time.
I'll play the other roles.
You will?
I'll show you exactly how to use your Sense.
My Sense?
How to use it?
Prince: Noa Hiiragi
The Little Mermaid:
Yae Niizuma
The Little Mermaid
Role
Actor
Yae Niizuma
Little Mermaid
Prince
Sea Witch
Noa Hiiragi
Yae, where are you off to in such a rush?
I'm looking for Hiiragi!
I wanted to rehearse with her!
Are you really going to stay?
Yes.
After this performance,
I'll step down from the stage.
From now on, please let me support
SIRIUS from behind the scenes.
But you're still young
and have a great Sense.
You have offers from various
other troupes, too, don't you?
If you transfer, I'm sure you'll find
your path to becoming a World Dai Star.
It was SIRIUS that shepherded me
down the path to acting.
Until SIRIUS produces a World Dai Star,
I have no plans to take the stage again.
I want to become a World Dai
Star as soon as possible.
Stella of the Theater:
The changed marks, lighting,
music cues, and direction...
You've got it all down now, right?
Kokona!
I'm fine.
What do you think?
Well, we'll need to make some minor
adjustments, but this should be fine.
Well, Kokona? Have you hit your limit?
No... I can keep going.
Okay. Then let's continue
rehearsing until you can't anymore,
to increase the precision of your Sense.
Yes, ma'am!
Arabian Nights
Sold Out   Thank You
That person totally cut in line!
I'm so glad I made it in time!
We get to see Yae, right?
I can't wait!
The curtain's rising, Kokona.
Yeah. I'm fine now.
Let's go, Shizuka.
The people in this town never look up.
They're too busy running their shops.
No one ever sees me.
No one even knows my name.
But...
I love this city!
Everyone's desperate to survive.
At night, they all get drunk to the music.
You can smell the sweet aroma
and hear the laughter...
See? It's starting again tonight.
Another Arabian night.
Make your dreams come true
Leggo!
Sing and dance to your heart's content
Did her acting skills go up another notch?
A mirage rises from the heat
Aladdin's presence on stage is stronger.
All I can rely on is my body
This feeling...
My earnest eyes just look ahead
It's the Prince from The Little Mermaid.
Um, when you say how to use my Sense...
When you played the Prince
from The Little Mermaid,
what were you thinking about, Kokona?
I was just so caught up in the moment...
I figured that was how Shizuka
would play the part.
It was a short scene, but you could
clearly tell what the Prince was feeling.
If you're just playing the role,
you can't express
what a character is feeling.
Shizuka must be strangely good
at blending into roles.
Your acting style is close
to perfect immersion.
Perfect immersion?
That might be the ideal type of
acting you want to adopt, Kokona.
Wait!
Let go of me!
What Aladdin feels here
is a faint sense of hope
after meeting Leila, who's from
a completely different world.
Just maybe, he can finally escape
his days of fighting for survival.
So...
Please.
I'd like to talk with
you for a little longer.
Will you live your whole life being poor,
or will you step forward into a new life?
The choice is entirely yours.
Aladdin knows nothing
about the outside world,
so everything outside
the city is unknown to him.
So to meet a mysterious man
who sees right through him...
He's nervous and anxious.
She's actually pale and shaking.
It's like she's truly terrified
to go into that cave.
Through Aladdin, even the
audience is feeling it.
To Kokona, Shizuka is the ideal actor.
All she needs to do now is put in
a little sweat to reach that ideal.
That's why I've drilled the basics into
Kokona these past three months.
I had her play a variety of roles
so she could gain experience.
This is the lamp he's after.
Finally, my life will be...
The comprehension to perfectly
draw out the emotions of a role.
The keen expressive ability to convey
those emotions to the audience.
The two of them together bring
the ideal performance to life.
That's...
our Sense!
I'm the Genie of the Lamp!
I serve whosoever possesses my lamp!
I shall grant you any
wish your heart desires!
You must be the genie from this lamp.
Yup!
You're in luck! You're one of a
select few who get to see my powers!
Let's start the music!
Gather the moments where the highlights burst
Surprise into when there was magic!
(So just special for you)
With everything just how you like it
A place where wishes came true,
that's the world we were in
(Dream like this come true,
dream like that come true)
(Ah) Even when I went into
the Lost Woods alone,
The atmosphere just completely changed.
It's like a concert.
Surprisingly, I was never scared
If you get swallowed up here,
this will be Niizumacchi's stage!
Because I've got adventure
(When I was little, the world was mysterious)
(Uh)
Your performance earlier was brilliant.
But I can't let you outshine me on this stage.
Wow! You're totally amazing!
Huh?
Show me more!
She's not fazed at all.
She's planning to play Aladdin as he is.
My heart just squeed.
You really surprised me!
When Kokona smiles, everyone smiles.
When Kokona speaks, everyone...
I'm looking forward to it!
Yae's flaw?
Yes.
No one's realized it yet, though.
Her Sense that allows her to express her
emotions to the audience through song
is entirely too powerful.
By the end of a show, the audience
will only remember Yae Niizuma.
But for a performance, that's...
The world will never acknowledge an actor
who destroys a performance as a Dai Star.
Um... Why are you telling us this?
Do you hear the revelry?
Everyone's intoxicated
by the Arabian night.
Just as you wished, Leila and I
are living happily ever after.
It's all thanks to you.
If I ever get to see you again...
No... No more wishes.
Yae's Genie was just like
I heard. She was super cute!
Merchandise Area
Right? I think it was
even better than before.
Especially that last scene
with Aladdin and the Genie!
Um! I'd like a picture of Aladdin...
Of Kokona Otori, please!
T-shirts 2,500 yen
Here you go. Thank you very much.
Was her name Kokona Otori?
I heard she's new, but she's pretty good.
I guess I was destroying the performances.
To think that I could do
just fine all by myself...
I was being vain.
If you want to become a World Dai Star,
I don't think you can do it alone.
Sadly, I realized that too late.
I'll become one no matter what.
I'll work together with
Kokona and the others.
So...
One day, will you join me again?
That's...
Hiiragi... and Yae?!
Did you need something?
Oh, um... Panda said
you'd probably be here.
Am I interrupting something?
We're done.
So, what do you need?
Um...
Thank you for helping me with my performance.
Don't be so off the cuff next time.
It's not good for my heart.
Yes, ma'am!
Kokona.
Yes?!
Thank you very much for helping me.
Huh?
Tonight's performance was wonderful.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow's
show as well, Kokona.
Yeah!
Whoa, Dugong?!
Wh-Wh-What? What?!
It appears as though Dugong
enjoyed the performance, too.
Is that what this means?
Hey! Now the fireworks have started!
Come on! You know that
was too awkward to butt in!
This is what people mean when
they say you need to read the room!
You were watching?!
Festival time, festival time!
Oh, I love festivals.
Festival time! Festival time! Festival time!
Fireworks!
They're very pretty.
Up they go!
Aladdin gets nervous
Make the Genie stand out
I'm the star!!
Without being swallowed up
by the Genie, Aladdin is totally moved
from the bottom of his heart!
Make sure you don't get upstaged by the Genie's lines!
Aladdin seems anxious
Make sure to be excited about new, unknown experiences!
Arabian Nights
Eighth Stage
Romeo and Juliet
Next time: "Romeo and Juliet."