Here.
SIRIUS Acting Troupe
We got another request this year.
Hozuki Ichi
The special theatrical showcase?
I guess it is that time already.
We're definitely...
getting our revenge this year.
Stella of the Theater:
Romeo and Juliet
An article about Arabian Nights?
Oh, yeah!
Did they say anything about you, Kokona?
Just a little.
"A performance of note
was Kokona Otori as Aladdin."
"Her Aladdin was overflowing with humanity,
and she captivated the audience."
That's amazing! This writer is famous
for being a super-harsh critic!
This means our acting
reached the audience, right?
Let's buy another copy.
Huh?
We need to send it to your parents.
Yeah!
When you think of summer...
This is the stuff.
It's a summer tradition.
So, how do you find things at SIRIUS lately?
I think things are relaxing quite nicely.
Koko-chan, Kathrin, and Niizumacchi all seem
to be affecting each other positively.
They're in top form now.
They sure are.
You know, I think we might just make it.
If we can keep this hype going,
we might be able to get
SIRIUS back to how it used to be...
Um, hello?
Hmm?
Keep it coming.
Today, we start rehearsal for our
annual special theatrical showcase.
Special theatrical showcase?
Every year, SIRIUS puts on a performance
for the grade school kids of Taito Ward.
We're looking for interested children,
and the chosen are invited to our troupe.
The showcase is also for the
purpose of nurturing future Dai Stars.
Remain focused in order to put on
a good show for your younger peers.
Hiiragi-san!
What is it?
Um... Has the play already been decided?
It's King Lear, same as last year.
I knew it...
The boss is dead set on it...
But doing King Lear
for grade schoolers is, uh...
We don't have much time to rehearse,
so I chose the same play.
Any objections?
What's King Lear about?
A king betrayed by his daughters
and exiled from his land
is taken by madness and slowly withers.
It's a tragedy about human absurdity.
If you have something to say, then say it.
Why are we doing King Lear for
a bunch of grade school kids?
She actually said it!
Excellent, Kathrin! You tell her!
King Lear is one of Shakespeare's
four great tragedies,
but it's famous for being
one of the most difficult.
Seems a bit much for children.
True, the play might be difficult,
but it's also important for kids to see the
classics when they're impressionable.
Will they even understand it?
It's our job to make sure they do.
It's no use...
At this rate,
the same tragedy will befall us!
I'm scared!
Take me home!
No!
I wanna go home!
What should we do?!
There has to be something we can do!
Panda...
When I was in grade school,
I saw King Lear at the National Theatre
in London and was deeply moved!
For sure! King Lear is an absolute classic!
I'm sure many would be moved by it!
But last year, the kids got scared
and cried in the middle of it!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Well, there isn't anything we can do—
Of course there is!
The point of the showcase
is to nurture future Dai Stars.
As Kathrin said, King Lear is a bit
much for grade schoolers.
So what we need to do is choose a play
that can move everyone and
get them to fall in love with theater!
I agree with Panda.
We do too!
I guess you have a point.
Victory!!
What in the world happened last year?
This is going to be a test performance,
so why don't we leave it to the girls?
All right, let's discuss what play to put on.
How about one like The Little
Mermaid that's based on a fairytale?
That's a great idea. SIRIUS
has quite a few in its repetoire.
If we want them to get a real taste of
theater, maybe it should be Shakespeare?
I think a comedy would be easier
for a child to understand than a tragedy.
Well, if it's a Shakespearean comedy we want...
Twelfth Night, As You Like It,
or Much Ado About Nothing, probably?
Hmm... We should probably go with
something a little more mainstream.
This is rather orthodox,
but how about Romeo and Juliet?
Romeo and Juliet is usually
considered a tragedy,
but it also has romantic comedy aspects.
The story is also very moving and easy to
follow, so I think they might enjoy it.
I think that's fine.
I'm sure they all know it.
It is pretty famous.
Sounds like we have our play.
We'll be doing Romeo and Juliet
for the special theatrical showcase.
What?!
You're not going to be in it, Yae-chan?!
Romeo and Juliet Roles
Romeo: Sasuga
Juliet: Panda
Benvolio: Kokona
Count Paris: Terahara
Friar Laurence: Kathrina
Tybalt: Kamiyashiki
Grade Schooler
Well, I'm in grade school too. I'll be in
the audience cheering you all on this time.
Count Paris: Terahara
Friar Laurence: Kathrina
Tybalt: Kamiyashiki
I'm playing another support role...
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
Romeo and Juliet brings back
a lot of memories for me,
so playing in it gives me
a lot to think about.
Sasuga-chan! I'll be Romeo's friend Benvolio.
I look forward to acting alongside you.
Same.
I can't wait to see you two star in this play.
I'm excited to learn from your performance.
No way! You saying that is...
Make sure you two show your
younger peers what you've got.
Hiiragi-san...
Boss...
I'm sure that girl will
be back again this year.
Ah...
So she's coming back.
The ward office said that she entered herself
in the ticket raffle hundreds of times.
Wh-What's wrong, you three?
She's coming.
Not you too, Sasuga-chan!
Menacing
Wait, everyone's doing it?!
Who are you all talking about?
Chika Nanase.
A grade school girl who goes
to about 400 plays a year,
earning her the nickname
"the Theater Professor."
She's why the boss really
wanted to do King Lear.
Did something happen?
After last year's show...
I truly felt SIRIUS's soul in making
a brave choice like King Lear so boldly.
But did you forget that your audience
today was grade school students?
With that in mind, you should have chosen
something to make SIRIUS shine.
As someone who's followed SIRIUS for years,
I was disappointed with this King Lear.
To quickly sum up everything wrong
with this performance in an hour...
She gave notes to Hiiragi-san?!
What a terrifying grade schooler...
She told us off, too.
Yup, yup.
So, Koko-chan!
We absolutely cannot lose this battle!
"Battle"?
Sassu! This time, we'll
really knock her socks off!
I'd love to make her
put a sock in it too.
We'll sock it to her, for sure!
We'll start rehearsal in ten.
Make sure you're ready!
Yes, ma'am!
Things seem to be taking shape.
They're so motivated...
Y-Yeah...
Stella of the Theater:
I know that voice...
Art thou not Romeo and a Montague?
Neither, fair maid, if either thee dislike.
And but thou love me...
This is just the first rehearsal,
but they're so in sync.
Not bad.
What's the matter?
I suddenly want to be up on stage.
My life were better ended by
their hate than death proroguèd,
wanting of thy love!
She's always so spacey, but she
completely changes onstage.
I used to be so jealous of Sassu,
who could do everything.
Sassu and I were childhood friends
who lived near each other.
We were always together.
That cloud looks yummy.
School's this way, dang it.
Ah...
So I always had a front-row seat
to how impressive she was.
Elementary School Art Contest
Special Award
Panda Yanagiba
Looky, looky, Sassu!
My picture got a special award!
First Prize
Chisa Sasuga
Seriously.
Seriously?
Seriously?!
Sasuga-chan, the swim team wanted you
as a backup swimmer, didn't they?
And you got scouted as a model?
Is it true that you found some edible ants?
Starting today, we're rivals!
Rivals?
It means we're enemies!
Oh...
Everyone just keeps talking about Sassu...
I'm special too!
Panda!
I'm not talking to you anymore, Sassu!
Why?
Because we're rivals!
Oh...
Special Theatrical Showcase
SIRIUS Acting Troupe's "Romeo and Juliet"
Anyone interested in the attending,
please send a request letter to the Taito Ward Office.
Wow!
Romeo and Juliet!
I'm so excited!
What are you doing?
There's a special theatrical showcase!
And SIRIUS is doing it!
SIRIUS is great!
SIRIUS...
Special Theatrical Showcase
Taito Ward
—SIRIUS Acting Troupe—
Romeo & Juliet
I won a ticket.
Once I get famous here,
I'll finally be able to...
Isn't this exciting?
Sassu?! Why are you here?!
I won a ticket too.
Let's go.
Huh? H-Hey!
That was amazing.
Yeah.
I wonder if I could be up on stage...
I wonder if I could be just like them.
I want to be on that stage!
I want to be a Dai Star!
Me too.
Huh?
If you're gonna do it, I want to do it too.
Why?
Why do you keep getting in my way, Sassu?
Art, the pull-up bars, even swimming!
How come you can do it all?
You can do everything better
than me... so why...
I want to see the same world as you, Panda.
You do?
You've got a good head on your shoulders
and you always think about others.
That's why I like you, Panda.
And?
Huh?
Say more of my good traits!
You're smart.
And?
And... And...
Oh, you're cute.
You should've said that first!
Oh, fine. I guess you're
just useless without me.
Let's do this, then! You'll become a Dai Star
with me, the world's cutest Panda!
Yeah!
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing. I was just reminiscing.
Monja Asakusa
It's been some time, Miss Niizuma.
Hello, Nanase-san.
Arabian Nights was fantastic!
Your performance was on par with the
actors of SIRIUS's golden age.
Thank you very much.
I wasn't very interested in this
production because you're not in it,
but I figured I could kill
some time since I won a ticket.
I hope this won't damage the renown
you earned with Arabian Nights.
It'll be fine. SIRIUS only delivers the best.
Oho?
They might even sock it to you.
Let's bring the house down, Sassu.
Let's go, Panda.
Two households, both alike in dignity,
in fair Verona, where we lay our scene...
The Capulets and the Montagues.
From ancient grudge break to new mutiny...
where civil blood makes civil hands unclean.
From forth the fatal loins
of these two foes...
whose misadventured piteous overthrows...
doth with their death bury...
their parents' strife.
They're following the original play
while adding a SIRIUS twist. Not bad.
O Juliet...
Did my heart love till now? Forswear it, sight!
For I ne'er saw true beauty till this night.
O Romeo, if you love me,
tell me from your heart...
Crap!
And it was all going so well
up until now. How disappointing.
Let us swear under the holy moon
the love from our hearts.
What?! That was part of the act?!
I've never seen such a beautiful
proposal from Romeo!
Chisa's Sense allows her to incorporate
any mistake made onstage
into part of the performance.
Her carefree nature turns it into
an elegant form of expression.
Romeo's so amazing!
Juliet is so pretty!
And Panda can control the stage
by reading the audience's mind.
When their two Senses
work together perfectly,
they take the crowd into
the palm of their hand.
Juliet! Juliet!
My love, my wife... I won't leave you
all alone in this tomb.
Thou detestable maw...
grant me sweet death!
Here's to my beloved Juliet!
Romeo?
Juliet? How?!
The friar gave me medicine.
Medicine to make it appear
as if I were no longer alive.
For if I were dead, I would be free
of my engagement to Count Paris.
We'd be free from our crimes.
And I could live my life with you.
Thank you, Juliet.
This love of ours should be able to end
the feud between our families.
Yes, Romeo.
This is...
This is the soul of SIRIUS!
Hey, Sassu.
Hmm?
Do you think we measured up
to that other performance?
I dunno, but...
Romeo & Juliet
Chisa Sasuga
I think this will make a great memory.
I hope so.
Ninth Stage
World Dai Star
Next time: "World Dai Star."