It's so muggy here in Japan.
Stella of the Theater:
Sasuga
Niizuma
World Dai Star
SIRIUS SENTO
Okay, I'll be back this evening.
Don't drown.
I've played a fish before,
so I'll be totally fine.
I'm not sure what to make of that...
So Sasuga's into surfing?
That girl honestly does everything.
She'll come back from a random walk saying,
"A stranger taught me how
to do this thing." Like that.
The other day, it was pottery,
and before that, it was amateur radio.
Sasuga
Niizuma
Currently, she's hooked on researching
morning glories and surfing.
I wonder if this is how she
prepares for her roles.
How'd ya like that?
You seem tired.
Did you stay up all night again?
It's summer vacay time for school,
and SIRIUS is on break until we
start prepping for the fall show.
All righty! Another day of checking
out the chatter about us on the net!
Gotta make sure none
of those anti-fans get popular!
I've been thinking about this for a while,
but Panda's kinda dangerous.
Hiiragi? Good morn...
What?!
W-Water...
I feel alive again. Thanks.
Um... What happened?
It was the strangest thing.
Those bottles hold a clear liquid, like water,
The Star of
Asakusa
yet no matter how much I drink,
I remain thirsty.
It just doesn't make sense.
Ah, so you drank too much.
Now that you mention it,
she does reek of alcohol.
Kokona, let's get some air in here!
Right!
I heard that you've been visiting
various troupes these past few days.
I have! I've been visiting an improv
troupe with Kathrina
where we can participate on the fly.
We're actually going again today.
That sounds fun.
It is!
Ever since Arabian Knights,
I've fallen even more in love with acting!
It's just so much fun!
Must be nice...
If I didn't have summer vacation
homework, I could've joined you...
Yae?!
What homework do you have today?
It's calligraphy, so I came by
to have Shamo teach me.
Tomorrow, I have sewing for home ec.
The day after that, I have kanji drills...
I guess grade-schoolers
have their own troubles.
Kathrina! We should get going.
No way!
What's up, Kathrina?
Is something the matter?
M-My mama just said... she's in Asakusa.
Mama?
Your mama?
Y-You don't mean...
Theresa Griebel is seriously here?!
What's a World Dai Star doing in Asakusa?!
Mama!
Kathrina!
It's been so long. I've missed you!
Me too, Mama.
S-So bright!
That's a World Dai Star for you!
Her aura's on another level!
It's just backlighting, you dummies.
Oh, my!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Theresa, Kathrina's mother.
You must be Kokona and Shizuka.
Kathrina's told me all about you.
Th-That's us.
It's nice to meet you.
Wow!
Huh?!
You can touch her and she can talk...
Is she really a Sense?
U-Um...
Mama?!
Theresa?!
Oh, I'm sorry. I was just so curious.
What a curious Sense.
Will wonders never cease?
Dugong?
Who's this little one?
Um... sort of a pet that belongs to SIRIUS.
Maybe more like a mascot.
Meet Dugong.
Dugong tagged along when we
said we'd be meeting you.
Be careful. That rodent bites.
I see...
I guess the little critter likes me!
Totally wrapped around your finger...
You little rodent...
World class...
So, why did you suddenly come to Japan?
You're pretty busy, Mama.
Well, I got some free time
and wanted to see my daughter.
Is that the only reason?
Yes. Though sadly, I have
to leave tomorrow morning.
Huh?
Oh, I know!
Do you girls know a lot about Asakusa?
Oh, yeah.
Then could you show me around?
It'd be a waste to come all the way to Japan
and not do anything touristy.
Right now?!
So with that settled, let's go!
I see you're as pushy as ever.
Kaminarimon
Okay, smile!
Why are we wearing yukatas?
Because we look cute in them.
People are really staring...
Well, there's a World Dai Star here.
What do you expect?
Come now! There's no time to waste relaxing.
Where are we going next?
Well, if you want the
real Asakusa experience...
This!
How traditional!
Goemon!
Theresa! Can I get a picture, please?
Oh, sure!
Was?
As long as you don't mind these
future Dai Stars joining me!
There we go.
Asakusa Hanayashiki
Asakusa Gate
Flower
Shooting Gallery
Ring Toss
Over here!
SIRIUS SENTO
They're doing touristy things in Asakusa?
Yes.
I imagine Theresa is dragging
Kokona and Shizuka around too.
Oh, it's for real.
It's trending all over social media.
"A World Dai Star appears!"
World Dai Star
-Yae Niizuma
I wish I could've met Theresa, too.
She contacted us saying that she
wanted a tour of SIRIUS,
so you can meet her later.
Then let's head to SIRIUS immediately!
You need to do your homework first.
Okay...
I need to concentrate on my work, too.
"SIRIUS girls enjoying their day off!"
Take that, antis! Behold my cuteness!
Got us some dinner
"Got us some dinner"?
The heck happened to surfing?
Stella of the Theater:
That was so much fun!
Thank you, Kokona and Shizuka.
No problem...
Theresa, you didn't sweat at all...
in spite of the heat.
World Dai Stars don't sweat.
That's what my mama told me.
She's definitely lying to you about that.
But she's so beautiful that
I'd actually believe it!
Yeah.
I thought I'd be just like her immediately...
Kathrina?
N-Never mind!
We've been waiting for you, Theresa.
I'm Noa Hiiragi. It's an honor to meet you.
Thank you for looking after my daughter.
Our troupe extended an invitation to you,
but I guess you turned us down.
I'm sad I can't perform with you.
I didn't think I was ready for it yet.
I see.
Is Shamo here?
She's inside.
Shamo!
Shamo! Shamo! Shamo! Shamo! Shamo!
It's been ages, Theresa.
I missed you so much!
I've missed you too. How long has it been?
Since before I married Tobias, so...
Since we costarred in A Midsummer
Night's Dream in Paris!
I played Puck and you played Titania!
What lovely memories.
I clearly remember you throwing a fit
because you wanted to be Titania.
I could play the role beautifully now,
but I still can't live up to your Titania.
Yeesh, she's definitely a World Dai Star!
Her aura's intense!
Super intense!
Is that what the kids say these days?
I came back in a rush.
Which do you think she'd like best as a gift?
U-Uh...
Maybe you should cook them first.
This is a lovely stage
that's hosted many actors.
I can feel its history.
Your daughter's also working hard right now.
Yes.
Thank you for letting her join your troupe.
Kathrina's talent is what got her in,
though she seems to be having
some growing pains now.
Excuse me.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Yae Niizuma.
Yae! I saw your performance!
Huh?!
As Princess Kaguya and the Genie of the Lamp.
Your closing show for Arabian Nights
was especially magnificent.
I-I'm honored...
So, um... We have a favor
to ask you, Theresa.
What is it? An autograph? Sure.
I'd love one! But...
Even just for a second...
could we see you perform?
Me?
Yes! We wanted to see
a World Dai Star's acting live.
Please!
Hmm...
If Noa will do it with me, sure.
Huh?!
The boss and Theresa are
going to perform together?
That's too epic!
Hiiragi...
Please, Hiiragi!
All right, just one scene.
Yay! That's amazing!
I wonder what they're going to perform.
I'm the one who brought you here
so that we could indulge
this passion together.
Your heart is under my control.
You can never turn back.
You can never even glance back at the past.
Give yourself to me.
What kind of desires will burn through us?
What kind of sweet temptations await us?
You were guiding me,
though I understood nothing...
Yet now I am here with you.
I will never turn back.
It's finally begun... our passion play!
It'll burn through us!
This is our final play!
The curtain rises!
The final play!
The final performance draws near!
We can no longer turn back, Christine.
Phantom...
What's your next line?
Why...?
I should be the one to play Don Juan.
Come... Let us fall to hell together!
I think that's about enough.
Sure.
Oh, crap... I seriously thought I
was at the opera house for a second.
Me too, even without a set or costumes.
My heart is pounding!
So that's how a World Dai Star performs...
She really is amazing.
Hiiragi was amazing, too.
I think she was playing her part
so we'd all be looking at Theresa.
She was truly like a phantom.
But right there at the end...
Come! Let us fall to hell together!
Something like that.
You sure got guts to imitate
that right after seeing it.
Nerves of orichalcum.
Huh?
U-U-Uh, I just...
It seems your Sense helps bring out
the performance of your costars.
Thanks to you, I was able to give
a show close to the original.
I appreciate it.
It was nothing.
I got to experience what it's like to work
with a World Dai Star's Sense again.
It's so far away...
The more you understand yourself,
the more your Sense will evolve.
I'll be waiting until then.
This was such a fun day.
Thank you so much for spending
it with me, Kathrina.
You're not going to say anything?
I thought you came here to scold me for
what a disappointment I've been.
I've done nothing of note
even after performing
in The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter,
Arabian Nights, and Romeo and Juliet.
I'm only getting attention because I'm
the daughter of a World Dai Star.
I haven't left any deeper
impression than that...
Even though Kokona has.
But you haven't been
cutting corners, have you?
No.
Then I don't see a problem.
You're doing your best.
You think so?
The reason I came to SIRIUS is to discuss
the future of Kathrina Griebel's work.
My work?
You've received a number
of offers from various troupes.
Huh?
They've seen your SIRIUS performances.
They know about your mishap in
Germany, but they still want you.
B-But that's so sudden...
Opportunities appear all the time
before you're actually ready.
Is there a reason you have to stay here?
I'll get you the papers
from the troupes later.
Give me your answer by the
time I leave Japan tomorrow.
I'll honor your wishes, no matter what.
Kathrina?
I'll become a Dai Star at SIRIUS
Our next performance will be
our last chance this year
to get the World Theatre League
to recognize a Dai Star.
Still, we've never had so much trouble
deciding on our fall show before.
The reasonable decision is to go with Yae.
Her acting skills are...
But Panda's not too shabby either.
I mean, she's so adorable, her Sense is
super awesome, and she's got plenty of fans.
We'll just have to go with Panda!
I'd really like that, myself.
Don't take me seriously!
What should we do?
Our upcoming fall production will be...
The Phantom of the Opera.
And we'll be holding auditions
for the role of the Phantom.
Tenth Stage
Everyone's Phantoms
Next time: "Everyone's Phantoms."