We'll be holding auditions for the Phantom.
Do not open
This time, everyone here will
get a shot at the role.
The Phantom... She means the Phantom, right?
I can't do it. There's no way
I can play that role.
Anyone who wants to try for the Phantom—
Hiiragi-san!
I want to audition!
The Phantom of the Opera is one of
SIRIUS's trademark productions.
I can't pass up on an opportunity like this!
If Panda's in, so am I.
Naturally, I'll be auditioning too.
What? No way...
I can't believe it.
Yae-chan?!
It can't be...
I'd like to audition, too.
No way. Yae playing the Phantom?
I figured she'd try for Christine.
So that's how it's gonna be, huh?
Still, no matter who I'm up against...
I absolutely...
...will not lose.
Anyone else?
I guess that's our pool—
Please wait!
I'd also like a chance
to be the Phantom!
Stella of the Theater:
Everyone's Phantoms
Panda, Chisa, Yae, Kathrina, Kokona.
You five will be auditioning.
The Phantom of the Opera
We'll then decide the supporting roles
based around the one playing the lead.
The audition will be in a week.
You're free to do as you like until then.
That's all for today.
Thank you very much.
We're going to be really busy.
Yeah!
Do you have a minute?
I want to talk to you about something.
Just the two of us, Kokona.
Huh?
Don't worry about me.
I'll review the script in the meantime.
Okay.
I'll see you in a bit, then.
The Phantom of the Opera
What did you want to
talk about, Kathrina-chan?
Kokona. How do you see me?
Huh? How do I see you?
I think you look cute. It really suits you.
Your rehearsal outfit, I mean.
I'm not talking about fashion!
I'm asking about my acting.
Your acting?
I'll just say it.
I'm envious of you, Kokona.
Huh?
You just keep growing.
It's blinding to look at.
I don't want to lose to you.
I can't.
Kathrina-chan...
Let's have a fair match.
Let's see who can take the role
of the Phantom... as rivals.
Okay. I won't lose.
Nineteenth century Paris.
Strange rumors are afoot
about the opera house.
A shadowy figure darts through the darkness.
A ghost who makes no sound,
dressed as a gentleman all in black,
appears out of nowhere.
He has a skull for a face.
Is he human or a devil?
Such rumors surrounding the Phantom
all have the ring of truth.
Christine is still a yet unknown singer
who lends her voice to the opera house's
prima donna, Carlotta.
The production is a huge success.
But all the praise goes
to Christine's singing.
Frustrated, Carlotta begins spreading
bad rumors about Christine.
Christine finds out about this
and is deeply hurt by it.
Then there's an accident.
Christine has a sensational debut.
Her voice charms Raoul, her childhood friend
who happens to be in the crowd.
They reunite and rekindle
their romantic feelings for one another
from their younger days.
But the Phantom cannot
allow them to be together...
for he was the one who'd awoken
Christine's vocal talent.
Driven mad by jealousy,
the Phantom kidnaps Christine
and heads deep into the abyss.
Some of this is definitely
a departure from the original,
but the Phantom is fundamentally the same.
The key here is how to portray
the anger and solitude
the Phantom feels being shunned
by society for his hideous face.
No one will love me.
No one understands me.
I shall channel my rage into song!
As my heart wills!
So that I may forget my loneliness!
Music? It must be the opera.
I cannot stand the sound of it.
Let me play!
I'll give you a true opera!
It should be me!
No, that's impossible...
I am but a shadow. A hideous monster.
Yae-chan?
The Phantom's étude of rage...
That was magnificent.
The Phantom of the Opera
We've only just received the scripts,
yet you're already so into the role.
I must say, I'm a bit jealous.
It's no big deal.
I've still got a ways to go.
I need to delve even deeper
to really get into the Phantom.
Won't you take part in the play, Shizuka-san?
Huh?
I mean, all of us
and the audience can see you,
so I don't see the problem
with you performing.
Don't you want to try to play the Phantom?
When I saw you acting just now,
I could feel your yearning to be onstage.
That'll never happen. I mean...
I'm Kokona's Sense.
I see...
Would you mind reading some lines with me?
Huh?
I suddenly feel like I want to be
in this production with you.
The Phantom of the Opera
Sure.
If you think I can do it.
The Phantom and Raoul both fall for Christine,
and she doesn't know what to do!
How unfair! I want to be loved too!
I thought you wanted to be the Phantom, Panda.
I do, but it'd also be fun to play Christine.
We only got bit roles
the last time we did this show.
We were just nameless ensemble characters.
The Phantom of the Opera
Playing the lead is nice, but the supporting
roles in the SIRIUS version are good too.
I know, right?
In the original story, the ballerina
Sorelli doesn't stand out too much,
but she's a key character here.
She's Christine's best friend and the only
one who knows about the Phantom's past.
Carlotta's also pretty dramatized, too.
The audience is supposed to despise her,
but she has a humanity to her
that makes her hard to hate. It's great.
I'm sure you could make her cute.
I think you'd be a decent Sorelli, Sassu.
It's basically a storyteller-type role,
and you're really convincing when
you're on the stage by yourself.
Hmm...
Audition for the Phantom role
in 7 days!!
We were supposed to be
thinking about the Phantom.
Yeah.
Stella of the Theater:
I guess that about does it.
I feel like I'm starting to see it.
I think I'm starting to get the role, too.
Thanks, Yae-chan.
I should be thanking you.
I want to try this with Kokona immediately!
I need to go deeper...
to become one with the Phantom.
The Phantom's parents abandoned
him when he was young,
selling him to a freak show
where he lived a horrible life.
They worked him ragged every single day,
and the drunken promoter would beat him.
He lost the will to live.
It was Sorelli who saved him.
She secreted the Phantom away
to the basement of the opera house.
That was where he came to know opera
and fell in love with Christine's singing.
I've still got so far to go...
What are you doing in my seat?
The fifth box at the
opera house belongs to me.
No one else is allowed to sit here.
But SIRIUS allows people up here sometimes!
SIRIUS's Phantom is rather generous.
Glad to hear it.
What made you decide to audition?
Just like when I asked to play the Genie,
I wanted to challenge myself.
To try for a role so unlike me.
Every true actor wants to play a role
completely unlike themselves.
Hiiragi-san, what do you want
to see in this audition?
The potential of Senses.
The clashing of your Senses
might give rise to something.
A performance far beyond what I could reach...
I knew it.
Now I really can't lose this audition.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you had been the Phantom, Hiiragi-san...
I would've loved to be your Christine.
Thank you.
How was that?
I mean, it was amazing.
I could really feel the Phantom's
rage and loneliness.
But...
You're not satisfied with this performance?
N-No, that's not it!
But I think there might be a
different way to approach it.
A different way?
Yeah. When I read the script,
the Phantom I envisioned
was sitting all alone in the dark,
hugging his knees.
He was so lonely and desperate.
I'm sure he just wanted
to be loved by someone.
I always have the same dream...
I'm walking under the sun
with nothing to hide.
I can dine out like normal people do.
I go to mass on Sundays and pray to God.
No matter how unsightly I am,
I still seek the light.
Playing the Phantom as a man
who's filled with dreams is...
That wasn't exactly great,
but how about something like that?
Oh, but your version was much more like
the classic Phantom of the Opera.
Maybe we should go with that instead...
No.
Huh?
We should portray your Phantom, Kokona.
But...
If we don't, we won't get this role.
Huh?
The most important part of playing
the Phantom is his negative emotions.
The rage and loneliness he feels
from being shunned from society
turn into madness
as he descends into the abyss.
She's able to figure out how she wants
to play roles all by herself now...
You want to observe?
Yeah, that's totally fine.
We have nothing to hide.
Come on in.
"Phantom"? Is that your name?
Yes, that's what my mother called me.
Let us eat. I just got
some excellent red wine.
The Phantom and Christine's meeting...
Why do you wear a mask?
One who can't hide their pain
with a mask of smiles
nor their delight with a mask of indifference
cannot consider themselves a true Parisian.
Let's just say it's for my amusement.
She's so cool!
Her Phantom is an elegant gentleman
despite the loneliness he feels.
Anyone else trying a stylish Phantom
would be at a disadvantage.
Next, Panda and Kamiyashiki.
Right!
Is this like a masquerade, then?
Indeed.
There are things in this world that
you're better off not knowing.
But I want to know...
more about you.
Don't touch me!
Listen well. If you want to live
here in peace, do not anger me.
She's playing the Phantom
exactly as he's written.
And with Panda's Sense,
she can give the judges
exactly what they want.
Their Phantoms were really something!
It's the same role,
but they made it totally different!
Now's not the time to be impressed.
You have to beat both of them!
Next up, Yae-chan and Kathrina are going
to be rehearsing on stage, so let's go watch.
Yeah!
Two shadows overlap as this melody wavers
Until we fall into the abyss
I will swear myself to you for eternity
Her Sense is always incredible.
Even our sins can be hidden
We need a way to hold our own
that isn't through song.
In this masquerade
Kathrina-san?
I hope you don't mind me
using the stage before you.
Hey, would you read lines with me?
They're...
Yae-chan's playing Christine?
I'm ready whenever you are.
Then let's do act 1, scene 9,
starting from when Christine wakes up.
Who are you?
An angel? Or a demon?
I want to know more about you.
Because you gave my song wings...
I want to get to know you.
You chose to come here.
There's no turning back now!
I'm sorry! I—
Huh?
Did she just... predict what
Yae-chan would do next?
The effectiveness of her Sense
has increased exponentially.
Take a good look at my
hideous face, Christine...
This repulsive visage
burned by the flames of hell!
Now you understand, don't you?
I am no angel. I am the Phantom
of the Opera that you all fear.
She upstaged Yae.
Kathrin...
She took the rage and loneliness
the Phantom held within for years
and turned it into madness.
That isn't a facade. It's real acting.
Seeing this just...
Don't you want to try to play the Phantom?
This feeling...
Thank you for playing Christine.
Kathrina-san, you—
Stay away!
The Phantom is still inside of me.
Everyone was so amazing.
Especially Kathrina-chan's Phantom.
I wonder how I can play a role like that.
I'm pretty sure my Phantom
isn't what the audience wants.
Care for a little trip?
Huh?
There's somewhere I want to go.
We can go after the audition—
It has to be right now.
Shizuka-chan?
I have to tell you something important.
Eleventh Stage
Our Promise
Next time: "Our Promise."