The Deep Blue Sea Is Everyone's Treasure
Wow!
We haven't even been away six months,
but this is so nostalgic.
I feel so relaxed now.
But should we really be here?
The audition is tomorrow...
This is necessary, though.
Huh?
Do you remember when you first said you
wanted to become a World Dai Star?
Um...
I think it was about when
I graduated middle school.
I wrote it on my future plans survey at school
and my teacher looked so done with me.
Oh, but I might've told
someone in class before that...
Huh?
I'm going to be a World Dai Star!
That's what I want to be!
I told someone even before that...
Well, I figured you didn't remember, but...
I'll tell you what you're missing, Kokona.
Huh?
The great age of theater...
This is the story of how to make
one girl's dream come true.
Stella of the Theater:
Our Promise
There was once a town
that was the beating heart of theater.
A town where actors and actresses
played all kinds of roles,
bringing countless stories to life.
A certain young girl lived there as well.
She loved picture books and the
stories her parents would tell her.
Eventually, she would become a storyteller
too and try various roles herself.
That's...
That was when the girl first saw...
a production put on by
actors called Dai Stars.
From that moment on,
she was captivated by the stage.
She went to the theater over and over
and reenacted the plays she saw there.
Sometimes, she was a knight
who swore fealty to the king.
Others, she was a young man madly in love.
She'd get too into her role on occasion
and cause trouble for the people around her.
Those were fun and happy days for her...
But they didn't last long.
We're moving?
Our house will be smaller than it is now?
But why? What about theater?
I see... The ocean?
Yeah, that sounds fun.
It's okay. I'll just go to see plays
by saving up my allowance.
And so the girl arrived in a new town
where the sea and sky stretched out forever.
The scenery was unfamiliar,
and so were the people.
The theater was so far away,
she had to take multiple trains to reach it.
Her parents were busy and didn't
come home until late into the evenings.
On top of that... she had trouble
making friends right away.
She was bored to tears when she was alone.
That's right.
I...
The little girl recalled the plays she'd seen
and brought that dream world back to her,
one performance at a time.
Day after day, she never tired of it.
But being by yourself is a lonely thing.
Then one day...
I remember now.
We finally met.
Could you do that one more time?
You must like acting. I love it too!
Then let's do it together!
The first friend I made after moving here...
She wasn't anyone from school,
and I could only meet her here.
She loved acting,
knew all the plays I had seen,
and was a better actor than me.
We always wanted the same roles,
and you'd always let me have them,
just because you thought I'd play them better.
And my friend would always get mad.
She'd tell me I wouldn't be able to play
a part well if I kept lying about how I felt.
That's right...
How did I forget all of that?
Maybe it was because
you couldn't control your Sense yet.
Not to mention that this was
the stage we had to work with...
Stage... my Sense?
I'm your Sense, Kokona.
The partner you created because you
needed someone to perform with.
And...
The receptacle for the feelings you couldn't
sustain after you lost your confidence.
The feelings I couldn't sustain?
I want to be on that stage.
I want the best role.
I want to outshine everyone...
Even if it means knocking other actors down!
I'm totally better!
My performance was perfect!
I want to be onstage more than anyone!
So... why?!
Why doesn't anyone see that?!
That's not what I—
You did think it!
I know your heart
better than anyone, Kokona.
But it's okay to feel that way. You're an actor!
Especially if you want
to become a World Dai Star.
Don't forget those feelings.
So...
Huh?
I'm going to return these feelings to you.
I can't take the stage,
so I shouldn't hold on to them.
No! I don't want them!
You keep them, Shizuka-chan!
I promise I'll play the roles
exactly how you tell me to!
You can't beat Kathrina and the
others with half-hearted acting.
But... I'm scared.
This is too sudden...
Without you, Shizuka-chan, I...
I told you from the start.
This is the story of how you make
your dream come true, Kokona.
I'm not the star, so my role ends here.
Shizuka-chan...
Shizuka-chan!
I know you can make it happen, Kokona.
I can't wait to see your Phantom.
Shizuka-chan...
Stella of the Theater:
It's almost time for the audition.
Yeah.
Kathrin, how's your right eye doing?
It's the worst.
Kokona-san...
Are the four of you ready?
Kokona was supposed to go first,
but if she's not here in time,
she's not fit to play the role.
Kathrina, I know you're not in your
best condition, but are you ready?
Yes, of course.
Then come up to the stage—
I'm sorry I'm late!
Please let me, Kokona Otori,
play the role of the Phantom.
You're always like this.
Kathrina, do you mind if Kokona goes first?
That's fine. I'm the one who's
going to win in the end.
Kokona, you'll be docked
points for being late.
Do you still want to audition?
Yes! Please let me do this!
I always have the same dream...
I'm walking under the sun
with nothing to hide.
I can dine out like normal people do.
This is the scene where
Christine takes off his mask
I go to mass on Sundays and pray to God.
and he becomes enraged but
also tells her how he feels.
No matter how unsightly I am...
Being on a real stage was blinding.
Kokona's growth was blinding.
I want to be up there too.
I wonder if I'll be able to stand on
that stage overflowing with light.
I still seek the light.
There's no rage or resentment.
This is how the Phantom
feels inside as a person.
Pure admiration for the stage?
To think she'd play the Phantom
with that look on her face...
I shall channel my rage into song!
As my heart wills!
So that I may forget my loneliness!
Music? It must be the opera.
I cannot stand the sound of it.
Let me play!
I'll give you a true opera!
It should be me!
That's the anger and loneliness
Shizuka-san portrayed.
No, that's impossible...
I am but a shadow.
A hideous monster.
I totally lost.
Are you crying?
No!
I gave that performance my all.
I have no regrets.
The loneliness and rage of the Phantom
hiding deep within the opera house...
I thought expressing that was the key to
showing the Phantom's fear and sadness.
The variations of the
Phantom we tried to play
are probably extensions
of Hiiragi-san's Phantom.
I'm sure that she saw new
potential in Kokona-san.
His heart's weakness, its purity...
The longing to step outside...
The annoyance, jealousy, and sadness
of being denied what he wants...
I'm surprised she played the role
in such a complex way.
I wonder what happened.
It must be... Shizuka-san...
Your Phantom was wonderful.
Shamo-san...
You don't look like an actor
who just got the role.
Seems you haven't been able
to shake off the Phantom yet.
I don't think I'll ever be able
to shake him off again.
That wasn't actually the Phantom.
It was the Shizuka-chan who
disappeared into my heart.
I see.
Is this really how an actor who wants
to become a Dai Star should be looking?
Huh?
Even after this production is done,
your time on stage won't come to an end.
I've watched many actors over
the years. That's how I know.
You still don't truly understand yourself.
To be on the stage
is to find yourself through acting.
Your Sense is born by facing the
brilliance that lies dormant within you.
Find myself...?
Why don't we go downstairs?
Have a seat.
Okay.
Close your eyes.
In front of you is your other self.
The person you need to talk to.
Go on, ask her. Ask her what
you want to do right now.
What I... want to do?
Why did I want to become
a World Dai Star again?
You even forgot something that important?
It's because you love the theater.
But that's not a rational thought to have.
They're, like, the best of the absolute best.
Well, you fell in love with them.
What can you do?
Besides, it's not just my dream.
Huh?
I would've lost hope if I'd been alone,
so I needed her.
Remember our promise.
It's no use. I've only ever
acted in front of my parents...
It's always easy to find reasons
not to do something.
You know that, Kokona.
What's important is how you feel!
How you feel, Kokona!
What do you want to do?
Me?
I'll give you some advice.
You need to say your dreams out loud.
Say you're going to make them come true
and make yourself believe it!
Make myself believe it? How?
It's easy.
Just play the part of a girl with dreams!
Play the part?
Become her!
All so you can make your dream come
true and become a World Dai Star.
What about you, Shizuka-chan?
Huh?
You're not going to be one, Shizuka-chan?
You're going to become one for me too!
Okay.
I'm going to be a World Dai Star!
That's what I want to be!
If I can become one,
I know you'll be one too, Shizuka-chan!
Then someday...
Someday, let's take the stage together!
It's a promise!
Yeah, it's a promise.
Someday, let's take the stage together...
Kokona-chan?
I'm going to go rehearse with everyone...
so that I can see Shizuka-chan again!
Koko-chan...
I have to work hard for Shizuka-chan, too.
I need to make The Phantom of the Opera
a success so I can become a World Dai Star.
So...
Please help me out, everyone!
I need your help!
The hell?!
You got nothing to worry about!
We're your friends, after all.
The only thing that should
be dense is French baguettes.
We'll rehearse with you lots!
Everyone...
Kokona!
You can have the role of the Phantom,
but this time, I'm going to upstage you!
You'd better be ready!
Kathrina-chan...
You're so young and edgy, Kathrin.
So edgy I might cut myself.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
That you're edgy.
No, really! What does that even mean?!
Twelfth Stage
The Two of Us Together
The final episode: "The Two of Us Together."