The Phantom of the Opera
The show will start once
dress rehearsals are over.
It's finally upon us.
The big performance.
Shizuka...
Have more confidence in yourself.
You beat all of us to
become the Phantom, Kokona.
And you've rehearsed like crazy.
Even the Phantom
isn't that harsh on Christine.
I stopped counting after
the tenth time you said,
"Sorry. Can we do that one more time?"
It was 23 times.
Let's show the Shizuka that's inside of you
what a waste it'd be to miss
out on a production like this.
Kathrina...
Yeah!
The Two of Us Together
Isn't this exciting, dear?
Yes.
SIRIUS's The Phantom of the Opera...
The last time I saw this was when
Noa Hiiragi was starring.
I'm excited to see
what the Phantom will be like.
Yeah, yeah! I'm getting excited, too.
The star is that rather dry Aladdin...
I hope you're able to
quench my thirst today.
The Phantom of the Opera
Huh?! Y-Y-You're—
Shh.
I haven't told my daughter I'm here.
How is our confidence level?
We won't know until the curtain rises.
It's rare to hear you sound so unsure.
I can't get Kokona's
performance out of my head.
A Phantom of mixed yearning and hatred.
When they said Shizuka disappeared,
it became obvious.
Producing a World Dai Star here at SIRIUS...
That selfish desire of mine
may have taken the Sense...
may have taken Shizuka from Kokona.
But even so, I didn't recast
the play because I still wanted to see
the Phantom that Kokona would play.
Even if it means she loses her Sense.
Senses represent possibility.
The ability to make dreams come true.
They're incredible, blinding powers.
Let us believe in those girls' brilliance.
Nineteenth century Paris.
Strange rumors are afoot
about the opera house.
Rumors... of the Phantom.
Everyone at the opera house knows of him,
but no one has ever actually seen him.
Now, listen carefully.
Don't you hear it?
The sad but beautiful song of the Phantom.
Christine! Christine!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I'll be counting on you
for tonight's concert as well.
U-Um, is it really okay for me to do it?
I'm only asking because it's you.
You're the only one worthy
of being my "ghost."
Of course! I'll sing from
the bottom of my heart!
Now go and hide behind the curtain.
Carlotta.
She's a terrible actress,
but she's quite the songstress.
I'll be making good use of her for a while.
Now, everyone!
Tonight's concert will have distinguished
guests from the government in attendance.
Let's make it a night to remember!
Dust dances around on this old stage
Her crushed toes make the floors creak
This is the only time I'll be your foil.
Dance, ballerina
(Inside my mind, inside your mind)
Kokona...
Shizuka mentioned to me before
that she shouldn't have gone up
on stage like she did
This empty audience, the soundless cheers
during The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter.
Huh?
When I watch you play the Phantom,
it reminds me of Shizuka back then.
The clock begins to move; now rise, curtain
Like the Phantom who bestowed Christine
with his dreams and vanished.
It'd be weird to have a Sense
that only exists to disappear, right?
She sways back and forth
That's nonsense.
Yeah.
In the moonlight, her shining beads
of sweat resemble jewels
Shizuka, I...
I have so much I need to tell you.
Pas de chat un deux trois,
until the day she can shine
Everyone, please stay calm!
That was just a little accident.
Why...
Richard! Take care of Carlotta.
The defiler of opera has exited the stage.
That voice... Are you the angel?
Do not turn around.
The show must go on.
Do not let the performance stop.
What should I do?
Let them hear you sing.
But...
Don't worry. I know you can do it.
Believe in me.
Dust dances around on this old stage
Her crushed toes...
Oh? Isn't this Christine's dressing room?
It is. Do you need something from her?
Who are you?
Christine! Do you remember me?
Maybe this will refresh your memory...
I'm the boy who retrieved
your scarf from the ocean.
I've been able to take the stage because
it's where Shizuka saw me off.
Raoul?! Is that you, Raoul?
Did you hear something just now?
Hmm? No, nothing.
But I had no idea how Shizuka felt.
So one more time...
Christine.
You wanted to see me, didn't you?
Y-Yes...
Then I shall invite you to my dwelling.
Behold how you look in that mirror!
I'm drowning...
I'm melting...
Into you...
Inside this dream
I question
I call you
You sing praises of my name,
just who are you?
Can you hear me?
I can hear you
It's the beginning of this despair
The curtain rises on this darkness
I'm scared
Even fear...
It's not fair
...can be sweet
My heart commits a taboo, aah
Wait... We didn't prepare
anything like that.
You are my angel
Two shadows overlap as this melody wavers
This feeling... It was the
same way with Theresa.
Until we fall into the abyss
I will swear myself to you for eternity
Even our sins can be hidden
Expressiveness polished
to the limit via one's Sense
In this masquerade
allows an actor to show everyone
the world they imagine.
I'm drowning...
Her Sense evolved...
I'm melting...
I always have the same dream...
I'm walking under the sun
with nothing to hide.
I can dine out like normal people do.
I go to mass on Sundays and pray to God.
No matter how unsightly I am,
I still seek the light.
Is there anything wrong with that?
I'm sorry I was so startled earlier.
I won't run away again.
So please, show me your face once more.
I see.
I thought the Phantom
was being indifferent here
because he didn't want
to talk about the past, but...
I don't think that's the only reason.
I think he loves spending time with
Christine and wants to make the most of it.
I realized that after hearing
your interpretation of the Phantom.
You really are amazing, Shizuka!
Again, you'll be the one
playing the part, Kokona.
Though it'd be the best if we
could perform together.
Kokona...
Stella of the Theater:
Shizuka.
Should the Phantom be here?
You're not done yet, but it's
been a great performance so far.
Far better than when
we rehearsed it together.
You really could become
a World Dai Star, Kokona.
I will someday.
The truth is, somewhere deep inside,
I didn't think I could do it.
I was entirely self-taught before SIRIUS,
and at auditions, I always I got told
I didn't have any Sense...
I didn't believe in myself.
That's why I forgot about you
and the promise we made.
But I believe now,
from the bottom of my heart.
Because we promised each other.
You can't make a promise without two people.
You said this was my story, Shizuka...
But it's actually our story.
What do you want to do, Shizuka?
Someday, let's take the stage together!
It's a promise.
Yeah.
I want to be up there...
alongside you, Kokona.
Let's go back to our stage!
I will protect you.
I will free you from that monster!
I will become your light.
I'm the one who gave you music.
I'm the one who rekindled your passion.
And this is what I get in return?
I won't stand for this...
I will not tolerate it!
May divine punishment befall
those who betrayed me!
I've written both a wedding hymn
and a funeral's requiem!
I can play either!
Please stop...
Will we all die together, or will you
spend the rest of your life with me?
The choice is yours!
Stop!
I would've chosen you
even if you hadn't done all this.
You're lying!
I'm not!
That can't be true!
You ran away from me!
You saw my face and fled!
I was just startled at first.
I'll never fear you again.
Because you're the one who gave me music.
You're my angel of music.
And... you're not alone anymore.
Why did you kiss me?
Because I love you.
Raoul! Are you all right?!
Yeah, I'm fine.
Christine, do you really...
Everyone must be worried. Let's go.
If you could work up the courage
to take one step forward,
I think the people would understand you.
Christine... I have a request for you.
What is it?
Tonight, onstage, will you sing
this song that I wrote?
It's the song we used in our lessons.
I'll ask if they'll let me sing it
at the curtain call.
Thank you.
Viscount Raoul, take Christine back.
I must defuse the bomb I set up.
All right, I will.
Phantom!
Erik... That's my real name.
Erik...
Erik, you'll come hear me sing, won't you?
I wouldn't miss it.
That's enough. I can't keep
her tied down any longer.
This is the first time in my life
I've ever been glad that I was born.
Thank you, Christine.
I love you from the bottom of my heart.
This music I just wrote is where my feelings
go when they have nowhere else to go
The faithful metronome continues
to carve an unchanging rhythm
Alone and unheard
This lonely yet free melody...
You're the only one who can give it flight...
Can you hear it?
Thank you, goodbye
I give you this farewell
song in parting, my beloved
This single red rose continues to
shine beautifully in my memories
Happiness, sadness
So that I never forget them,
I change my body and soul into music
These wavering days fall into the abyss,
proving that I was alive
Our eternity starts to play our end
That was amazing. For a moment there,
I forgot I was watching a play.
We're probably not the only ones who forgot.
I'm sure the performers did, too.
You've gained a wonderful rival, Kathrina.
My body is tingling?
SIRIUS really...
My emotions are conflicted...
I'm moved but also anxious.
Phantom!
That was such a lovely performance!
As long as there are actors,
there will always be plays.
As long as there are plays,
Senses will continue to evolve
and actors will shine bright.
Wanting to see that light might be
what brings people to the theater.
They are truly radiant.
You've only gotten started yourself, my dear.
You flatter me.
No, this is really amazing, Niizumacchi!
You actually got chosen as a Dai Star!
I want to sleep with it.
That might actually bring good luck!
Can we borrow it for a night?
Nope.
Why did Niizuma get it when Kokona's
the one who played the Phantom?
During the play, I was able to channel
Christine from the bottom of my heart.
Yeah, I get that.
We totally got carried away
by Koko's Sense.
Being in The Phantom of
the Opera felt real nice.
That's not what I meant.
Anyway, I mean,
Koko's already got quite a record.
You don't need to get upset on her behalf.
I-I-I'm not doing it for her!
Girls!
We've decided on our next production.
Will there be another audition?
If you're overly disappointing,
I'll fail all of you.
Then would you star instead, Hiiragi?
Well, if you're all that disappointing...
Oh, come on. Surely you jest.
This time, I'm going to be the star!
I got myself some good luck.
Hey, that's no fair, Sassu!
Me too! Gimme some good luck!
I hope it brings you great fortune.
Where are Kokona and Shizuka?
It's so nice and cool...
Hey, won't we get in trouble for this?
Kathrina is always using the stage
to rehearse, so we should be fine.
You think so?
I wonder what the next production will be.
Whatever it is, we'll be the stars.
W-Wow, you're confident.
Well, we decided we'd take it.
Yeah!
Become World Dai
Stars together!!!!
Become World Dai Stars together!!!!
The two of us together!